<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game id="12119">
		<path>./Mario Kart 8.m3u</path>
		<name>Mario Kart 8</name>
		<desc>Mario Kart 8 is the 8th installment of the Mario Kart series, for the Wii U console.nnnnThe gameplay includes thirty-two circuits (sixteen brand new ones and sixteen retro ones) on which the characters race riding a variety of vehicles like the returning motorcycles from Mario Kart Wii or the karts, which can be customized.</desc>
		<image>./images/Turbo-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Turbo-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Turbo-marquee.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20140530T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
		<md5>1357c833acd98ec03218eb773296824a</md5>
	</game>
	<game id="12115">
		<path>./Super Smash Bros Wii U.m3u</path>
		<name>Super Smash Bros. For Wii U</name>
		<desc>Mario! Link! Samus! Pikachu! All of your favorite Nintendo characters are back, along with plenty of new faces, in Super Smash Bros. for Wii U, the next entry in the beloved Super Smash Bros. series.

Up to four players can battle each other locally or online across beautifully designed stages inspired by classic Nintendo home console games. With a variety of control options and amiibo compatibility, the timeless Super Smash Bros. battles come alive.</desc>
		<image>./images/cross_f-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/cross_f-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/cross_f-marquee.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20141121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Sora Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
		<md5>f47219d76c0a4c0e00289158519bf28c</md5>
	</game>
	<game id="12160">
		<path>./Yoshi's Woolly World.m3u</path>
		<name>Yoshi's Woolly World</name>
		<desc>Yoshi's Woolly World is a platform game in which the player assumes the role of Yoshi. Similar to developer Good-Feel's previous title Kirby's Epic Yarn, the game is set in a world where the characters and environment are composed of yarn and cloth. Yoshi retains much of his moveset from the Yoshi's Island series of games, including using his tongue to swallow enemies and using his flutter jump to reach hard areas, and many elements such as flowers and mystery clouds return. However, unlike other games where swallowing enemies would produce eggs which Yoshi could then throw, Yoshi instead produces balls of yarn.</desc>
		<image>./images/pj023-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/pj023-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/pj023-marquee.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<developer>Good Feel</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
		<md5>992d0288dd746aabd53803216ab5b75e</md5>
	</game>
	<game id="12149">
		<path>./Donkey Kong Country Tropical Freeze.m3u</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country : Tropical Freeze</name>
		<desc>Donkey Kong Country: Tropical Freeze is the fifth game in the Donkey Kong Country series and was released exclusively for Nintendo Wii U and later ported to the Nintendo Switch.nnnnWhile celebrating Donkey Kong's birthday the Kong family witnesses how an invasion fleet of arctic creatures (Snowmad) arrives. The island is frozen over and their flagship takes position on top of the island. This can't go unpunished so the Kong family is off to take back the island.</desc>
		<image>./images/rs10_production-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/rs10_production-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/rs10_production-marquee.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20140221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Retro Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>236ba24c45c026beb1f04edb3e39c407</md5>
	</game>
	<game id="12121">
		<path>./Bayonetta 2.m3u</path>
		<name>Bayonetta 2</name>
		<desc>Bayonetta 2 is the sequel to Bayonetta. You play as Bayonetta, an Umbran Witch who is out to rescue her friend Jeanne from the depths of Inferno. The game is set a few months after the events of the first game. Along the way she has to battle a host of angels and demons who are out to stop her. This is a 3rd-person action game in the mold of Devil May Cry or God of War, fighting multiple enemies and combining different moves based on melee combat and gunplay. The game is all about pulling off fantastic combos with precise timing as you face a number of memorable battles in a variety of locations.</desc>
		<image>./images/PRJ_010-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/PRJ_010-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/PRJ_010-marquee.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20141024T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>PlatinumGames</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>97f64e73426fe55969678e76516ff1cb</md5>
	</game>
	<game id="12119">
		<path>./Mario Kart 8.m3u</path>
		<name>Mario Kart 8</name>
		<desc>Mario Kart 8 is the 8th installment of the Mario Kart series, for the Wii U console.nnnnThe gameplay includes thirty-two circuits (sixteen brand new ones and sixteen retro ones) on which the characters race riding a variety of vehicles like the returning motorcycles from Mario Kart Wii or the karts, which can be customized.</desc>
		<image>./images/Turbo-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Turbo-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Turbo-marquee.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20140530T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<md5>1357c833acd98ec03218eb773296824a</md5>
	</game>
	<game id="246329">
		<path>./New Super Mario Bros U + Super Luigi U.m3u</path>
		<name>New Super Mario Bros. U + New Super Luigi U</name>
		<desc>Get two huge games in one bundle with this pack, which includes both the New Super Mario Bros. U and New Super Luigi U games.

New Super Mario Bros. U is a side-scrolling adventure featuring Mario, Luigi, Toad and your Mii™ character.

Up to five players can jump into the fun, with up to four people using Wii Remote controllers and one on the Wii U GamePad. Using the GamePad, a player can create Boost Blocks out of thin air to help other players, or access hard-to-reach items.
Boost Mode also makes cooperative speed runs possible for the first time. Use the GamePad to interact with and manipulate enemies and objects in real time, and discover new ways to find the fastest route through each stage.
In addition to the main Story Mode, in which players must rescue Princess Peach™, there are three more exciting game modes, including Boost Rush, Challenge Mode, and Coin Battle Mode.</desc>
		<image>./images/red-pro2-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/red-pro2-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/red-pro2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20151015T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Run Jump Scrolling</genre>
		<players>5</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<md5>28fd96523326565d0df4e211e413fd15</md5>
	</game>
	<game id="241512">
		<path>./The Legend of Zelda - Breath of the Wild.m3u</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild</name>
		<desc>Forget everything you know about The Legend of Zelda games. Step into a world of discovery, exploration and adventure in The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild, a boundary-breaking new game in the acclaimed series. Travel across fields, through forests and to mountain peaks as you discover what has become of the ruined kingdom of Hyrule in this stunning open-air adventure.</desc>
		<image>./images/U-King-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/U-King-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/U-King-marquee.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20170303T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<md5>f9f6f4f47bdcc98ba764c0e9960ae03f</md5>
	</game>
</gameList>
