<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Half-Life 2.lnk</path>
		<name>Half-Life 2</name>
		<desc>1998. HALF-LIFE sends a shock through the game industry with its combination of pounding action and continuous, immersive storytelling. Valve's debut title wins more than 50 game-of-the-year awards on its way to being named "Best PC Game Ever" by PC Gamer, and launches a franchise with more than eight million retail units sold worldwide.NOW. By taking the suspense, challenge and visceral charge of the original, and adding startling new realism and responsiveness, Half-Life 2 opens the door to a world where the player's presence affects everything around them, from the physical environment to the behaviors even the emotions of both friends and enemies.The player again picks up the crowbar of research scientist Gordon Freeman, who finds himself on an alien-infested Earth being picked to the bone, its resources depleted, its populace dwindling. Freeman is thrust into the unenviable role of rescuing the world from the wrong he unleashed back at Black Mesa. And a lot of people he cares about are counting on him.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Half-Life 2.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Half-Life 2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Half-Life 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20041411T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Valve</developer>
		<publisher>Valve</publisher>
		<genre>First Person-Shooter</genre>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alltynex Second.lnk</path>
		<name>Alltynex Second</name>
		<desc>The year is 2192AD. 40 years ago, the Stellar-class All-purpose Administrative Computer ALLTYNEX suddenly attempted to enact genocide upon mankind.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Alltynex Second.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Alltynex Second.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Alltynex Second.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20141201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Siter Skain</developer>
		<publisher>Nyu Media</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zaccaria Pinball.lnk</path>
		<name>Zaccaria Pinball</name>
		<desc>Zaccaria was founded by three brothers (Marino, Franco, and Natale) and was the 3rd largest manufacturer of pinball machines in the world (behind Bally and Williams). They had created and produced more than 35 different pinball machines between 1974 and 1987. Zaccaria Pinball is a commemoration of this great pinball manufacturer. In a nutshell: never-to-be-forgotten pinball experience! Why do we say that? Because #1: all 38 pinball tables are modeled with 100% accuracy from the original pinball machines of Zaccaria company Because #2: all sound effects, musics and vocals are recorded from the original pinball machines of Zaccaria company Because #3: all rules are scripted based on the rule sheets of the original pinball machines of Zaccaria company Because #4: a unique customization system gives you a free hand by many possibilities of change on graphical and physical parts of the game Because #5: various game modes ensure you to receive an amazing pinball experience independently of what pinball skills you have</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Zaccaria Pinball.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Zaccaria Pinball.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Zaccaria Pinball.png</marquee>
		<rating>4</rating>
		<releasedate>20160616T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Magic Pixel KFT.</developer>
		<publisher>Magic Pixel KFT.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./198X.lnk</path>
		<name>198X</name>
		<desc>Over-the-top arcade action meets coming-of-age drama, blurring the lines between game and reality.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/198X.png</image>
		<video>./snap/198X.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/198X.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20191201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hi-Bit Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Sonka</publisher>
		<genre>Arcade</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Adventure Pinball.lnk</path>
		<name>Adventure Pinball: Forgotten Island</name>
		<desc>It starts when you receive a note and map from your long lost grandfather, along with the promise of the adventure of a lifetime. You'll encounter dinosaurs, volcanoes, and man-eating sharks, as well as a tribe of cavemen to save.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Adventure Pinball.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Adventure Pinball.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Adventure Pinball.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20111201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Extremes</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Pinball</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Akane.lnk</path>
		<name>Akane</name>
		<desc>Akane is an Arena Arcade-Slash where you kill your enemies with only 1 hit. The objective of the game is simple, to kill as many enemies as possible.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Akane.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Akane.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Akane.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20181201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ludic Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Ludic Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Another World 20th Anniversary Edition.lnk</path>
		<name>Another World 20th Anniversary Edition</name>
		<desc>This is an updated version of Another World for the 20th anniversary of the original game, five years after the updated 15th anniversary edition. It is adapted for mobile devices offering both touch controls and a virtual D-pad.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Another World 20th Anniversary Edition.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Another World 20th Anniversary Edition.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Another World 20th Anniversary Edition.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20131201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DotEmu, Eric Chahi</developer>
		<publisher>Focus Home Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Broforce.lnk</path>
		<name>Broforce</name>
		<desc>When evil threatens the world, the world calls on Broforce - an under-funded, over-powered paramilitary organization dealing exclusively in excessive force.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Broforce.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Broforce.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Broforce.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20151201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Free Lives</developer>
		<publisher>Devolver Digital</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform, Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crimzon Clover - World Ignition.lnk</path>
		<name>Crimzon Clover - World Ignition</name>
		<desc>Take the role of a skilled pilot in the fight to destroy massive waves of enemies while dodging their unending rain of bullets. Each of the three ships has their own style of standard firing and a unique appearance.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Crimzon Clover - World Ignition.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Crimzon Clover - World Ignition.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Crimzon Clover - World Ignition.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20111201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Yotsubane</developer>
		<publisher>Degica</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./DOOM64 EX.lnk</path>
		<name>DOOM64 EX</name>
		<desc>Doom64 EX is a reimplementation of Doom 64 by Samuel "Kaiser" Villarreal. It is based on Doom3D, though rewritten for OpenGL rather than DirectX, and including some bug fixes from Boom and MBF.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/DOOM64 EX.png</image>
		<video>./snap/DOOM64 EX.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/DOOM64 EX.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.99</rating>
		<releasedate>20081201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>id Software</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Horror, Shooter</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nex Machina.lnk</path>
		<name>Nex Machina</name>
		<desc>Nex Machina is an intense arcade style twin-stick shooter from Housemarque. Taking hints from both Robotron and Smash TV, Nex Machina focuses on pure action, voxel destruction and competition in the distant, cablepunk themed future. Housemarque, the creators of Resogun, and Eugene Jarvis invite you on a trip back to the age of arcades and play Nex Machina, the twinstick shooter of this generation. Destroy the evil robots, free the humans and defeat your friends' high scores along with their dreams of success. Do you have what it takes to make it to the top?</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Nex Machina.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Nex Machina.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Nex Machina.png</marquee>
		<rating>4.56</rating>
		<releasedate>20170620T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Housemarque</developer>
		<publisher>Housemarque</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./PAC-MAN Battle Royal.lnk</path>
		<name>PAC-MAN Battle Royal</name>
		<desc>Release in the Arcade as 4 player madness! The 17th arcade game in Pac-Man's series (11th official). It is made as part of Pac-Man's 30th Anniversary and developed by Namco Bandai Games</desc>
		<image>./mixart/PAC-MAN Battle Royal.png</image>
		<video>./snap/PAC-MAN Battle Royal.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/PAC-MAN Battle Royal.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20111201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Arcade</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Project AETHER First Contact.lnk</path>
		<name>Project AETHER First Contact</name>
		<desc>As a threat from beyond looms over the solar system, take control of the AETHER prototype in this rhythmic and tactical space shooter - fusing classic arcade-style action with stunning 3D environments and an engaging sci-fi story.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Project AETHER First Contact.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Project AETHER First Contact.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Project AETHER First Contact.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>20201201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Arcade-Shooter</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Raiden IV - OverKill.lnk</path>
		<name>Raiden IV - OverKill</name>
		<desc>The series that changed the history of arcade shoot’em ups is back with the crazed action of Overkill mode! Master a variety of new weapons as swarms of enemy fighters try and put you down. Everything from fan favorites, such as the Spread Shot and Vulcan Laser, will be available, as well as new weapons and items! Instill fear in your enemies with devastating attacks and earn the acclaimed title of Master Ace! Game Modes OverKill Mode - a brand-new mode with new mission stages and a revamped scoring system! Additional Mode - Variation of Arcade Mode with 2 new stages Score Attack Mode - High Score Mode for all stages including those from Overkill Mode Arcade Mode - Arcade Mode that recreates the arcade experience with two difficulties: Light and Original World Rankings - Ranking mode that will place you among players from all over the world in Overkill Mode, Additional Mode, and Arcade Mode. Reply and Gallery - Watch Reply data and view items in the Gallery ??? - A secret mode playable once you clear the game Features Challenging New Bosses and Stages - With new stages and never before seen bosses, experience the fast, blistering game play action that never gets old. Items, Weapons, and More - Unlock and master a variety of weapons, including fan favorites such as the Spread Shot and Laser, and never before seen weapons and items! Best Graphics to Date - The series has transitioned from its 2D roots to 3D, creating lush environments, devastating explosions and countless enemies, without a drop in frame-rate.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Raiden IV - OverKill.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Raiden IV - OverKill.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Raiden IV - OverKill.png</marquee>
		<rating>3.48</rating>
		<releasedate>20150903T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Moss Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>H2 Interactive Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shovel Knight - Treasure Trove.lnk</path>
		<name>Shovel Knight - Treasure Trove</name>
		<desc>Shovel Knight: Treasure Trove is the full and complete edition of Shovel Knight, a sweeping classic action adventure game series with awesome gameplay, memorable characters, and an 8-bit retro aesthetic! Become Shovel Knight, wielder of the Shovel Blade, as he runs, jumps, and battles in a quest for his lost beloved. Take down the nefarious knights of the Order of No Quarter and their menacing leader, The Enchantress. But that’s not everything! Shovel Knight: Treasure Trove will feature three additional campaigns that are games all unto themselves! Take control of Plague Knight, and Specter Knight on adventures of their own, with King Knight joining later as a free update! Together, they form a grand and sweeping saga! With a fully cooperative campaign, a full-featured challenge mode, body swap mode, and a 4 player battle mode (Coming soon!) you’ll be digging for a long time. With Shovel Knight: Treasure Trove, you get it all. Uphold the virtues of Shovelry, earn relics and riches, and discover the true meaning of shovel justice!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Shovel Knight - Treasure Trove.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Shovel Knight - Treasure Trove.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Shovel Knight - Treasure Trove.png</marquee>
		<rating>4.2</rating>
		<releasedate>20170303T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Yacht Club Games</developer>
		<publisher>Yacht Club Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players />
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Speedball 2 HD.lnk</path>
		<name>Speedball 2 HD</name>
		<desc>Speedball 2 HD is a modern reincarnation on the classic, futuristic cyberpunk sports game Speedball, originally developed by the Bitmap Brothers and first released for the Atari ST in 1990. A brutal mix of handball and ice hockey placed at break-neck pace. Now Tower Studios, Vivid Games and The Bitmap Brothers have created a glorious fusion of classic gameplay and modern technology to launch this game into the 21st century. Choose from 28 teams across 6 new Speedball Arenas, Speedball 2 HD includes all the intense gameplay of the original with new teams, more formations and in particular the new Fire, Ice and Cyber teams.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Speedball 2 HD.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Speedball 2 HD.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Speedball 2 HD.png</marquee>
		<rating>3.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20131205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vivid Games</developer>
		<publisher>Mastertronic</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./The Fall.lnk</path>
		<name>The Fall</name>
		<desc>The Fall is the first game in a trilogy where the protagonist is artificial intelligence called A.R.I.D. It is part of a high-tech combat suit worn by a character called Colonel Josephs and uses a female voice. It activates itself after crashing on an unknown planet and since the user of the suit does not respond, her routines immediately kick in, and she seeks medical attention to save the pilot. Since the AI has full access to the suit functions, she can take over control. The game is played in a 2D side-scrolling environment. The suit can be moved left or right and it can jump as well. The environment can be examined using a flash light where the beam can be guided in any direction. It highlights interactive parts of the world, which can then be interacted with. Interactions include conversations with multiple dialog options, interacting with computers and tools, examining the environment and picking up objects. Most of the game however is based around puzzle-solving. It is story-driven and often focuses on how ARID struggles with her internal instructions combined with the directive to save the pilot. In some situations this shows her inability for nuance or lies. A Caretaker who now controls the facility sees her as faulty and aims to refurbish her. A large part of the game for instance shows how ARID needs to pass tests in unique ways to show her proficiency as a household robot, to show her willingness to comply. There are also many other dangers next to the Caretaker, such as security robots, fish, slugs and poisonous fungi. Much of the story and the facility's background is revealed through notes and conversations with computer systems.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/The Fall.png</image>
		<video>./snap/The Fall.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/The Fall.png</marquee>
		<rating>3.83</rating>
		<releasedate>20140530T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Over The Moon</developer>
		<publisher>Over The Moon</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./The Mummy Demastered.lnk</path>
		<name>The Mummy Demastered</name>
		<desc>A powerful ancient evil has arisen, and the war to save humanity has begun! The Mummy Demastered throws you into a 16-bit-inspired battle against the undead in a 2D, nonlinear, action-packed adventure. As an elite agent in the monster-hunting Prodigium organization, you must use a variety of weapons, upgrades, and mysterious artifacts to defend mankind against the supernatural hordes of Princess Ahmanet. Your Prodigium unit is already on the scene, but HQ lost contact with them hours ago. Only by exploring tombs, forests, abandoned tunnels, and the cursed streets of London will you discover the fate of your allies. But beware - Ahmanet commands legions of undead, insects, plague-ridden vermin, and worse! If you're not careful, you'll be the next soul in her army.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/The Mummy Demastered.png</image>
		<video>./snap/The Mummy Demastered.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/The Mummy Demastered.png</marquee>
		<rating>3.94</rating>
		<releasedate>20171024T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>WayForward</developer>
		<publisher>WayForward</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./The Typing of the Dead.lnk</path>
		<name>The Typing of the Dead</name>
		<desc>Could you kill a zombie with your bare hands? The faster you type, the quicker you'll kill and killing zombies is not only fun but rewarding.  A blistering fury of exploding Zombie flesh awaits your every key stroke.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/The Typing of the Dead.png</image>
		<video>./snap/The Typing of the Dead.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/The Typing of the Dead.png</marquee>
		<rating>4.83</rating>
		<releasedate>20131029T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Modern Dream</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wild Guns Reloaded.lnk</path>
		<name>Wild Guns Reloaded</name>
		<desc>Wild Guns Reloaded welcomes back Clint and Annie, the dynamic shooting duo from the 1994 original game, as they prepare to blast their way through several levels of gangsters and big, bad biomechanical bosses while collecting loot and dodging gunshots and the occasional creeper with an old-fashioned knife. This time around, they’re joined by a pair of surprising new heroes</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Wild Guns Reloaded.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Wild Guns Reloaded.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Wild Guns Reloaded.png</marquee>
		<rating>3.72</rating>
		<releasedate>20170711T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NATSUME ATARI Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Fighter X Tekken.lnk</path>
		<name>Street Fighter X Tekken</name>
		<desc>As fights go on, players build up power in a three sectioned meter at the bottom of the screen. Players can use a single section to use an EX attack, or tag with a partner during a combo, or use a full meter to perform a Super Combo. Players can also charge up special moves such as Ken's Tatsumaki Senpuu Kyakku and perform Tag Super Combos with their partner.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Street Fighter X Tekken.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Street Fighter X Tekken.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Street Fighter X Tekken.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20121201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./WWE 2K Battlegrounds.lnk</path>
		<name>WWE 2K Battlegrounds</name>
		<desc>The world of WWE is your battleground with all-new, over the top, in-your-face arcade action as your favorite WWE Superstars and Legends battle it out in outlandish interactive environments around the world. Compete in your favorite match types with an arsenal of exaggerated maneuvers, special abilities, and devastating power-ups, including Steel Cage, Royal Rumble, Fatal Four Way and more, as Mauro Ranallo and Jerry “The King” Lawler call all the mayhem! Are you ready to enter the battleground? Brawl Without Limits!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/WWE 2K Battlegrounds.png</image>
		<video>./snap/WWE 2K Battlegrounds.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/WWE 2K Battlegrounds.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20201201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Saber Initiative</developer>
		<publisher>2k Sports</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Fighting, Sports</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wetlands.lnk</path>
		<name>Wetlands</name>
		<desc>This game is very like Cyberia; the moving path is predictable, and all you have to do is shoot at anything that moves, and enjoy the animated sequences in between every mission. The time is set somewhere in the near future, and there is a major war active on your planet. By the time war is battling, the infamous and most dangerous international prisoner was rescued, and the prison guards were killed. As much as you don't want to participate in that action (since you're more interested in winning the war), you, as a great undercover agent are sent to bring the prisoner back. No matter the cost. As you can guess by the title, most action is taken under the water, and a few rare are battled in the space above. Bring him back commander!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Wetlands.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Wetlands.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Wetlands.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19951201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hypnotix</developer>
		<publisher>New World Computing</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Contra - Rogue Corps.lnk</path>
		<name>Contra - Rogue Corps</name>
		<desc>CONTRA is back! Two years after the Alien Wars ended, the Damned City erupts from the final battleground. From the midst of the chaos, a group of scoundrels emerge. They might not be typical heroes, but they're here to save the world… or get rich trying. Featuring action packed battles, customisable gear, gigantic bosses and explosive multiplayer action. Features: - Local CO-OP action for up to 3 players.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Contra - Rogue Corps.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Contra - Rogue Corps.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Contra - Rogue Corps.png</marquee>
		<rating>3.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20170926T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./AeternoBlade.lnk</path>
		<name>Aeterno Blade</name>
		<desc>In the region of Awelsia, vengeful Freya travels with an unknown weapon called "AeternoBlade" to take revenge from Beladim, the Lord of the Mist who destroyed her village, Ridgerode, and killed her tribe. Her vengence is helped by Vernia , who has as much merit as Beladim. Vernia taught Freya about the ablility of AeternoBlade. Freya has to venture in many world dimensions to find how to annihilate Beladim. What is AeternoBlade and How can Freya take revenge from Beladim? Solve tons ton of mysteries in her adventure!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/AeternoBlade.png</image>
		<video>./snap/AeternoBlade.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/AeternoBlade.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20141201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Corecell Tech</developer>
		<publisher>Corecell Tech</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Back To The Future The Game.lnk</path>
		<name>Back to the Future Episode 1: It's About Time</name>
		<desc>Marty McFly and Doc Brown return in a completely new Back to the Future adventure. Six months after the events of the third film, the DeLorean Time Machine mysteriously returns to Hill Valley - driverless!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Back To The Future The Game.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Back To The Future The Game.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Back To The Future The Game.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20101201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Telltale Games</developer>
		<publisher>Telltale Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Balls of Steel.lnk</path>
		<name>Balls of Steel</name>
		<desc>You'll flip out over the coolest, fastest, most innovative quicksilver ball-basher in the known universe! Across five savage, fully-animated tables, from the ricochet riot of Firestorm to the intense overload of Duke Nukem, Balls of Steel delivers.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Balls of Steel.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Balls of Steel.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Balls of Steel.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>20191201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Threaks</developer>
		<publisher>Wild River</publisher>
		<genre>Action Roguelike</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battle Planet - Judgement Day.lnk</path>
		<name>Battle Planet - Judgement Day</name>
		<desc>Battle Planet - Judgement Day is a planetary rogue-lite top-down shooter. You are one of the universe's 3 most wanted criminals on the run.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Battle Planet - Judgement Day.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Battle Planet - Judgement Day.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Battle Planet - Judgement Day.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19971201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wildfire Studios</developer>
		<publisher>GT Interactive Software</publisher>
		<genre>Pinball</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Black Future '88.lnk</path>
		<name>Black Future '88</name>
		<desc>Black Future ’88 is a Synth-Punk roguelike 2D action Shooter. Vertically climb an always evolving procedural tower to reach the top and kill its insane owner…before your heart explodes. Shoot, slash, dash and upgrade yourself to survive the endless.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Black Future '88.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Black Future '88.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Black Future '88.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20191201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Superscarysnakes</developer>
		<publisher>Good Shepherd Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blasphemous.lnk</path>
		<name>Blasphemous</name>
		<desc>A foul curse has fallen upon the land of Cvstodia and all its inhabitants - it is simply known as The Miracle. Play as The Penitent One - a sole survivor of the massacre of the ‘Silent Sorrow’.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Blasphemous.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Blasphemous.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Blasphemous.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20191201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>The Game Kitchen</developer>
		<publisher>Team17 Digital Ltd</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blazing Chrome.lnk</path>
		<name>Blazing Chrome</name>
		<desc>In Blazing Chrome, bring your best pal and kick some metal butts to free the humankind while enjoying a classic run’n’gun, fully loaded with action and exciting fights!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Blazing Chrome.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Blazing Chrome.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Blazing Chrome.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20191201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>JoyMasher</developer>
		<publisher>The Arcade Crew</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chasm.lnk</path>
		<name>Chasm</name>
		<desc>Welcome to Chasm, an action-adventure game in which you play a new recruit undertaking your first mission for the Guildean Kingdom. Thrilled to prove your worth as a knight, you track strange rumors that a mine vital to the Kingdom has been shut down. But what you discover in the mining town is worse than you imagined: The townspeople have disappeared, kidnapped by supernatural creatures emerging from the depths. Honor-bound to solve the mystery and restore peace to the Kingdom, you embark upon an epic adventure, with deadly battles against cunning monsters, exploration of ancient catacombs and castles, and powerful new equipment hidden at every turn. Though the overall story is the same for all players, your hero's journey will be unique: each of the rooms has been hand-designed, and behind the scenes Chasm stitches these rooms together into a one-of-a-kind world map that will be your own. Key Features - Explore six massive procedurally-assembled areas from hand-crafted rooms - Enjoy challenging retro gameplay and authentic pixel art (384x216 native res.)</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Chasm.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Chasm.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Chasm.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20181201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bit Kid, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Bit Kid, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Platform, Role-Playing</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Children of Morta.lnk</path>
		<name>Children of Morta</name>
		<desc>Children of Morta sets its story in a distant land but copes with themes closer to our daily lives that one would expect. It is a story of simple emotions we all know so well and value more than sometimes we dare to admit: love and hope, longing and uncertainty, ultimately loss and sacrifice we are willing to make to save the ones we care the most for. Embark on the adventure of an extraordinary family of heroes. With the Corruption spreading through the land, guardians of the Mountain Morta have to stand up against the ancient evil. But... it's not a story about saving the universe. It’s a story about a valiant family standing together while the world around them is being devoured by darkness.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Children of Morta.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Children of Morta.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Children of Morta.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20191201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dead Mage</developer>
		<publisher>11 bits Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, RPG</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cloudpunk.lnk</path>
		<name>Cloudpunk</name>
		<desc>Your name is Rania. This is your first night working for Cloudpunk, the semi-legal delivery company based in the sprawling city of Nivalis. You go everywhere, from the Marrow below to the spires that pierce the grey clouds high above before scraping the edge of the troposphere. No delivery job is too dangerous, and no one is faster than a Cloudpunk driver. In this story-based exploration game, you will meet a diverse range of characters including androids, AI and unscrupulous humans at every level of society. Everyone has a story, and in the course of one night in Nivalis, everything will change.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Cloudpunk.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Cloudpunk.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Cloudpunk.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20201201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ion Lands</developer>
		<publisher>Ion Lands</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Command and Conquer - Red Alert.lnk</path>
		<name>Command and Conquer - Red Alert</name>
		<desc>What if Hitler never existed? Einstein pondered the question and created a time-machine to eliminate Hitler as a young man, thus preventing World War II as history remembers it.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Command and Conquer - Red Alert.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Command and Conquer - Red Alert.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Command and Conquer - Red Alert.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19961201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westwood Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Command and Conquer - Tiberian Dawn.lnk</path>
		<name>Command and Conquer - Tiberian Dawn</name>
		<desc>Tiberian Dawn features three factions, each with its unique strengths and tactics; the Global Defense Initiative GDI, the Brotherhood of NOD and The Forgotten, a non-playable neutral faction of mutants who have been physically and mentally affected by the Tiberium.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Command and Conquer - Tiberian Dawn.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Command and Conquer - Tiberian Dawn.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Command and Conquer - Tiberian Dawn.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>19991201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westwood Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dark Quest 2.lnk</path>
		<name>Dark Quest 2</name>
		<desc>Dark Quest 2 is a turn based RPG where you control a party of heroes on your epic quest to defeat the evil sorcerer and his minions. Dark Quest 2 is a turn based RPG inspired by legendary board game Hero Quest.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Dark Quest 2.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Dark Quest 2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dark Quest 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20181201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Brain Seal Ltd</developer>
		<publisher>Brain Seal Ltd</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Diablo II+LoD.lnk</path>
		<name>Diablo II + Lord of Destruction</name>
		<desc>Diablo II was wildly successful, Blizzard chose to make an expansion that will add a fifth Act, featuring six quests in the Barbarian Highlands. Two unique classes, the female Assassin and the male Druid, will be available featuring new skills.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Diablo II+LoD.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Diablo II+LoD.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Diablo II+LoD.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.99</rating>
		<releasedate>20011201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Blizzard Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Blizzard Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dream Pinball 3D.lnk</path>
		<name>Dream Pinball 3D</name>
		<desc>A great pinball game should not only be amazing from the start, but should continue to be entertaining every time you play it. This was the thinking behind the development of the newest pinball sensation to hit the PC.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Dream Pinball 3D.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Dream Pinball 3D.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dream Pinball 3D.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20081201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TopWare</developer>
		<publisher>SouthPeak Games</publisher>
		<genre>Pinball</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Drifting-Lands.lnk</path>
		<name>Drifting-Lands</name>
		<desc>Drifting Lands is an hybrid of classical horizontal shoot'em'up with a lot of strong gameplay elements coming straight from the action-RPG genre. If you want an original diablo-like game or you want a different kind of shoot'em'up, you're in the right place!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Drifting-Lands.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Drifting-Lands.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Drifting-Lands.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20171201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alkemi</developer>
		<publisher>Alkemi</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./DriftOn.lnk</path>
		<name>DriftOn</name>
		<desc>DriftOn is an infinite racing game in the surreal fracturing world. You drive through terrain that keeps breaking apart. Crumbling race track introduces its challenges that test speed of your reaction and skill of predicting the road in its fractured state.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/DriftOn.png</image>
		<video>./snap/DriftOn.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/DriftOn.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>20201201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SPokeDev</developer>
		<publisher>SPokeDev</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Epic Pinball - The Complete Collection.lnk</path>
		<name>Epic Pinball - The Complete Collection</name>
		<desc>You will love the sound effects and bouncing action of this PC version of pinball. All the elements of the classic game are preserved, including the concentration of keeping your ball rolling, tilting the tables and getting all the right combinations of letters and channels to score maximum.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Epic Pinball - The Complete Collection.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Epic Pinball - The Complete Collection.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Epic Pinball - The Complete Collection.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>19931101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Extremes</developer>
		<publisher>Epic MegaGames, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Pinball</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./FATE Undiscovered Realms.lnk</path>
		<name>FATE Undiscovered Realms</name>
		<desc>Fate: Undiscovered Realms is an action role-playing roguelike video game developed by WildTangent and released on July 17, 2008, as a stand-alone expansion to the 2005 PC game Fate.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/FATE Undiscovered Realms.png</image>
		<video>./snap/FATE Undiscovered Realms.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/FATE Undiscovered Realms.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>20081101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>WildTangent</developer>
		<publisher>Encore Software</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fight'N Rage.lnk</path>
		<name>Fight'N Rage</name>
		<desc>Fight’N Rage is a brand new old-school side-scroller beat’em up. Inspired by the classics from the “golden age”, and with an art style that mimics the aesthetic from the 90's arcade gems, this game pays homage to all classic gameplay features that makes this genre one of the best from its time!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Fight'N Rage.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Fight'N Rage.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Fight'N Rage.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20171101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>sebagamesdev</developer>
		<publisher>sebagamesdev</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>3</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Foregone.lnk</path>
		<name>Foregone</name>
		<desc>Foregone is a fast and fluid 2D action-platformer packed with legendary loot and stunning pixel art, created and published by Big Blue Bubble.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Foregone.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Foregone.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Foregone.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20201201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Big Blue Bubble</developer>
		<publisher>Big Blue Bubble</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Guacamelee Super Turbo Championship Edition.lnk</path>
		<name>Guacamelee Super Turbo Championship Edition</name>
		<desc>The definitive version of the smash hit Metroidvania-style action-platformer, Guacamelee! STCE adds new levels, powers, challenges and refinements to the sprawling, ridiculous, Mexican-inspired adventure of the original Guacamelee!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Guacamelee Super Turbo Championship Edition.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Guacamelee Super Turbo Championship Edition.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Guacamelee Super Turbo Championship Edition.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20131201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DrinkBox Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gun Crazy.lnk</path>
		<name>Gun Crazy</name>
		<desc>Gun Crazy is a fast paced and hectic arcade style action shoot em' up, sporting old school pixel art and a retro sound track.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Gun Crazy.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Gun Crazy.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Gun Crazy.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20191201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ritual Games</developer>
		<publisher>GrabTheGames</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Halo - Combat Evolved Anniversary.lnk</path>
		<name>Halo - Combat Evolved Anniversary</name>
		<desc>Halo: Combat Evolved Anniversary comes to PC as the second installment of Halo: The Master Chief Collection. Now optimized for PC, relive the spectacularly remastered edition of the original Halo campaign, created in celebration of the 10th anniversary of one of the most beloved franchises in gaming history.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Halo - Combat Evolved Anniversary.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Halo - Combat Evolved Anniversary.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Halo - Combat Evolved Anniversary.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.99</rating>
		<releasedate>20201201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>353 Industries</developer>
		<publisher>Xbox Game Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Huntdown.lnk</path>
		<name>Huntdown</name>
		<desc>In the mayhem-filled streets of the future where gangs rule and cops fear to tread, only the bounty hunters can free the city from corruption. Lay waste to the criminal underworld and make a killing in this hard boiled action comedy arcade shooter.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Huntdown.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Huntdown.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Huntdown.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20201201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Easy Trigger</developer>
		<publisher>Coffee Stain Publishing</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kung Fury - Street Rage.lnk</path>
		<name>Kung Fury - Street Rage</name>
		<desc>Get blown into another dimension as you experience the gutbusting fun of the KUNG FURY: STREET RAGE game. Beat the nazis to stop Kung Führer and uphold the law! BECOME THE ACTION! BECOME KUNG FURY!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Kung Fury - Street Rage.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Kung Fury - Street Rage.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Kung Fury - Street Rage.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20151201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hello There AB</developer>
		<publisher>Hello There AB</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bloodstained - Ritual of the Night.lnk</path>
		<name>Bloodstained - Ritual of the Night</name>
		<desc>Bloodstained: Ritual of the Night is a gothic horror action side-scrolling RPG set in 19th century England. A paranormal force has summoned a demon-infested castle, revealing crystal shards infused with tremendous magical power. Play as Miriam, an orphan scarred by an alchemist's curse which slowly crystallizes her body. To save humanity, and herself in the process, Miriam must fight through the castle and defeat the summoner, Gebel. Collect, craft and unlock a vast array of weapons, equipment and loot to defeat the countless minions and bosses of hell that await!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Bloodstained - Ritual of the Night.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Bloodstained - Ritual of the Night.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Bloodstained - Ritual of the Night.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20191201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ArtPlay</developer>
		<publisher>505 Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Half Life 2.lnk</path>
		<name>Half Life 2</name>
		<desc>At the start of the game, the G-Man speaks to Gordon Freeman in a hallucination-like vision as he pulls Gordon out of stasis and places him on a train going to City 17. When the train arrives, Gordon gets off and proceeds through the Combine's security checkpoints where he is detained by a civil protection officer. Once in an interrogation room, the officer reveals himself to be Freeman's former co-worker and colleague, Barney Calhoun who is working undercover, and helps Freeman to get to Dr. Isaac Kleiner's laboratory. After meeting Alyx Vance, Freeman is instructed by Kleiner to step into a makeshift teleporter so that he can be safely extracted to the anti-Combine resistance base Black Mesa East along with Alyx, headed by her father, Dr. Eli Vance. However, Kleiner's pet headcrab Lamarr disrupts the machine, and Freeman finds himself — after briefly appearing in several different locations — just outside Kleiner's lab. With the Combine now alerted to his presence, Freeman works his way through the drained canal system, avoiding enemy forces and using the help of human resistance fighters  to safely arrive at Black Mesa East.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Half Life 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Half Life 2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Half Life 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20041116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Valve Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Valve Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>a3e50f5c743505f9a84f8b3ec43336a1</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ion Fury.lnk</path>
		<name>Ion Fury</name>
		<desc>3D Realms, creators of Duke Nukem 3D, Prey, and Max Payne, are excited to team up with Voidpoint to bring back the legendary Build Engine, famously known for classic first-person shooters like Duke Nukem 3D, Shadow Warrior, and Blood. Ion Fury is the real deal! While Shelly “Bombshell” Harrison earned her codename defusing bombs for the Global Defense Force, when evil transhumanist mastermind Dr. Jadus Heskel unleashes the members of his cybernetic cult onto the streets of Neo DC, she knows it’s time to start causing explosions instead of preventing them.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ion Fury.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Ion Fury.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ion Fury.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20191201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Voidpoint, LLC</developer>
		<publisher>3D Realms</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Juanito Arcade Mayhem.lnk</path>
		<name>Juanito Arcade Mayhem</name>
		<desc>Arcade Mayhem Juanito is a retro experience about arcade-hopping. Teleport into different video games, play with unique mechanics inspired by well-known arcade games, face stunningly animated bosses and join the fight against the clonocell invasion.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Juanito Arcade Mayhem.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Juanito Arcade Mayhem.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Juanito Arcade Mayhem.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20171201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Ever Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Game Ever Studio</publisher>
		<genre>Arcade</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./LIMBO.lnk</path>
		<name>LIMBO</name>
		<desc>Uncertain of his sister's fate, a boy enters LIMBO. Winner of more than 90 awards, including GameInformer's Best Downloadable, GameSpot's Best Puzzle Game, Kotaku's The Best Indie Game, GameReactor's Digital Game of the Year, Spike TV's Best Independent Game, X-Play's Best Downloadable Game and IGN's Best Horror Game.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/LIMBO.png</image>
		<video>./snap/LIMBO.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/LIMBO.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20111201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Playdead</developer>
		<publisher>Playdead</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Puzzle</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man Zero - ZX Legacy Collection.lnk</path>
		<name>Mega Man Zero - ZX Legacy Collection</name>
		<desc>Mega Man Zero/ZX Legacy Collection brings together six classic titles in one game: Mega Man Zero 1, 2, 3 and 4, as well as Mega Man ZX and ZX Advent.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Mega Man Zero - ZX Legacy Collection.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Mega Man Zero - ZX Legacy Collection.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Mega Man Zero - ZX Legacy Collection.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20171201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megamagic - Wizards of the Neon Age.lnk</path>
		<name>Megamagic - Wizards of the Neon Age</name>
		<desc>Prepare to delve into a fascinating world where the forces of technology and magic are embroiled in a vicious struggle! Blurring the lines between the RPG and strategy genres, Megamagic recaptures the unmistakable flavour of the 80s in a game filled with pop culture references and magnified by the incredible music by Mitch Murder, composer of Kung Fury and Hotline Miami 2 soundtracks.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Megamagic - Wizards of the Neon Age.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Megamagic - Wizards of the Neon Age.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Megamagic - Wizards of the Neon Age.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20161201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Beautifun Games</developer>
		<publisher>Beautifun Game</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Neon Abyss.lnk</path>
		<name>Neon Abyss</name>
		<desc>Neon Abyss is a frantic, roguelike action-platformer where you run ‘n’ gun your way into the Abyss as part of the Hades formed ‘Grim Squad’. Featuring unlimited item synergies and a unique dungeon evolution system, each run diversifies the experience and every choice alters the ruleset. Get ready to unleash hell! Evolving Dungeon With each run, you will be able to unlock new rooms, items, bosses, special rules and even new endings!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Neon Abyss.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Neon Abyss.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Neon Abyss.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20201201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Veewo Games</developer>
		<publisher>Team 17 Digital Ltd</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Neon Chrome.lnk</path>
		<name>Neon Chrome</name>
		<desc>Neon Chrome is a top-down cyberpunk shooter with roguelike elements. It takes place in Neon Chrome, an arcology (large tower) built by Neon Corp where millions of people live. The player takes control of one of the inhabitants flagged for removal. He connects to one of thousands of assets through an immersion chair to bring down the system, with a new asset for every session, from a selection of three.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Neon Chrome.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Neon Chrome.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Neon Chrome.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20161201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>10tons Ltd</developer>
		<publisher>10tons Ltd</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing, Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NeuroVoider.lnk</path>
		<name>NeuroVoider</name>
		<desc>NeuroVoider* is a twin-stick shooter RPG set in a cyber futuristic world about brains shooting around evil robots with nuclear rocket launchers. Battle through the horde of vigilant robots, boost your character with the smoking remains of your victims, and defeat the master NeuroVoider to end this eternal war. Play it coop with up to 4 friends, or go alone in an adventure of hack'n'slash rampage, with a pinch of rogue-lite, and some permadeath. * may contain explosions.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/NeuroVoider.png</image>
		<video>./snap/NeuroVoider.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/NeuroVoider.png</marquee>
		<rating>3.33</rating>
		<releasedate>20160831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Flying Oak Games</developer>
		<publisher>Plug In Digital</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing, Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NyxQuest - Kindred Spirits.lnk</path>
		<name>NyxQuest - Kindred Spirits</name>
		<desc>Fly with Nyx across the ruins of the ancient Greece in her dangerous search for her dearest friend Icarus. Use the powers of Zeus and the Gods from Olympus and use them wisely in order to help Nyx to complete her epic adventure.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/NyxQuest - Kindred Spirits.png</image>
		<video>./snap/NyxQuest - Kindred Spirits.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/NyxQuest - Kindred Spirits.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>20100927T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Over The Top Games</developer>
		<publisher>Over The Top Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Oceanhorn - Monster of Uncharted Seas.lnk</path>
		<name>Oceanhorn - Monster of Uncharted Seas</name>
		<desc>You wake up and find a letter from your father. He is gone… The only lead is his old notebook and a mysterious necklace. What happened? Oceanhorn: Monster of Uncharted Seas combines captivating storytelling, breathtaking 3D visuals and exciting gameplay into one epic action-adventure experience. In the game you explore the islands of Uncharted Seas, a world filled with many dangers, puzzles and secrets. You must fight monsters, learn to use magic and discover ancient treasures, which will help you on your quest. Use all of your wits and skill to unravel the mysteries of the ancient kingdom of Arcadia and the sea monster, Oceanhorn.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Oceanhorn - Monster of Uncharted Seas.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Oceanhorn - Monster of Uncharted Seas.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Oceanhorn - Monster of Uncharted Seas.png</marquee>
		<rating>4.05</rating>
		<releasedate>20150317T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cornfox and Brothers</developer>
		<publisher>FDG Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Oniken.lnk</path>
		<name>Oniken</name>
		<desc>When a global war nearly decimated humankind, an evil military organization called Oniken takes advantage of the situation to dominate and oppress the few remaining survivors. Even though any resistance to this organization seemed hopeless, a small rebel movement organizes strikes against Oniken. One day, a ninja mercenary named Zaku offers his services to the resistance for unknown reasons. His moves are lethal and now he is the resistance's only hope.  Don't Worry, You Will Die A Lot Of Times.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Oniken.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Oniken.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Oniken.png</marquee>
		<rating>4.2</rating>
		<releasedate>20120621T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>JoyMasher</developer>
		<publisher>JoyMasher</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./PAC-MAN Championship Edition 2.lnk</path>
		<name>PAC-MAN Championship Edition 2</name>
		<desc>The much-awaited sequel to PAC-MAN™ CHAMPIONSHIP EDITION! Featuring eye-popping 3D graphics and funky visuals, the latest version of the classic game takes chomping and chasing through mazes to a whole new level! Make up to four ghost trains for maximum chompage! New modes include Score Attack and an Adventure Mode with fast fleeing fruit, big bad bosses, ridiculous remixed rules, and more!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/PAC-MAN Championship Edition 2.png</image>
		<video>./snap/PAC-MAN Championship Edition 2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/PAC-MAN Championship Edition 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>3.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20160913T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai Namco Studios Inc</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./PAC-MAN Championship Edition DX Plus.lnk</path>
		<name>PAC-MAN Championship Edition DX Plus</name>
		<desc>It's time to gear up!  A Pac-Man experience that will definitely surprise you!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/PAC-MAN Championship Edition DX Plus.png</image>
		<video>./snap/PAC-MAN Championship Edition DX Plus.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/PAC-MAN Championship Edition DX Plus.png</marquee>
		<rating>4.12</rating>
		<releasedate>20130924T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco Bandai Games</developer>
		<publisher>Namco Bandai Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./PAC-MAN256.lnk</path>
		<name>PAC-MAN256</name>
		<desc>PAC-MAN 256 is the maze that never ends. But the Glitch is coming for you… Get Lasers too!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/PAC-MAN256.png</image>
		<video>./snap/PAC-MAN256.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/PAC-MAN256.png</marquee>
		<rating>3.94</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>BANDAI NAMCO Studios Vancouver</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Project Warlock.lnk</path>
		<name>Project Warlock</name>
		<desc>One man and his guns. Become a mysterious Warlock who embarks onto a dangerous mission to eradicate all evil. Put your finger on the trigger and travel through time and space to wreak havoc like in the golden days of fast paced, adrenaline-pumping first person shooters, hooking you for hours of super fun carnage. Let’s rock and roll!  Develop your hero the way you like, by assigning upgrade points and perks to the favorite skills between each level. Develop and upgrade spells and weapons to create your unique character through the game, and use their powers to master the game in higher difficulty modes.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Project Warlock.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Project Warlock.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Project Warlock.png</marquee>
		<rating>3.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20181018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Buckshot Software</developer>
		<publisher>gaming company</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Punch Club.lnk</path>
		<name>Punch Club</name>
		<desc>Punch Club is a sporting management simulation in which the player manages an upcoming boxer in training and preparation for a series of boxing matches at a local club, while searching for clues of who killed their father. The game was developed as a humorous take on action films of the 1980s and 1990s. The player controls an unnamed boxer whose father, who helped to train him, was murdered. The boxer aims to continue his training and become the best boxer at a local league, while following clues to lead him to who killed his father. The player manages the boxer around the clock through various locations in a city, including his home, the boxing gym, stores, and his work place. Time progresses when the player is involved in any activity, including moving between these locations.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Punch Club.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Punch Club.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Punch Club.png</marquee>
		<rating>3.12</rating>
		<releasedate>20160109T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Lazy Bear Games</developer>
		<publisher>tinyBuild</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting, Role-Playing, Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rad Rodgers.lnk</path>
		<name>Rad Rodgers</name>
		<desc>Rad is a rambunctious but spirited young boy who maybe plays too many video games. After dozing off at the tail end of a long night of gaming, Rad awakens to find his dusty old console has turned itself back on. Suddenly a vortex emerges and he's sucked into his TV, where he finds himself the star in his very own video game adventure. Dusty is Rad's good-hearted but foul-mouthed, now-sentient game console. His clock speed isn't what it used to be, but what he lacks for in megahertz he makes up for with experience and attitude! Rad and Dusty's adventure begins in the First World, taking them through seven dangerous stages of action-packed, humor-filled, hardcore platforming fun. This decaying jungle world has been infected by a fierce corruption, and it's up to the unlikely buddy-duo Rad and Dusty to save the jungle's inhabitants and restore the Elder Tree as guardian of the land. Weapons: Dusty arms Rad with a variety of radical bad-ass weaponry. The Bolt Blaster has unlimited ammo, is easy to use, and more than enough firepower to get the job done. The Phoenix Cannon shoots out a fiery bird whose wingspan lights enemies ablaze as it flies by. There are 5+ weapons in this first chapter, with more to come. Sounds and Music: Our composer Andrew Hulshult combined his years of musical experience (both performing and writing) with his passion for retro-style gaming to create an amazing and authentic soundtrack for the game complete with MIDI-inspired music... And synthesizers! The Pixelverse: While Rad and Dusty are a great team, only Dusty can enter the electrified Pixelverse -- a dangerous spacetime-breaking region that exists behind the game world. Dusty enters the Pixelverse when necessary to repair glitches in the running game world, allowing both Rad and Dusty to continue their journey. Classic Easter Eggs: The game features hard-to-find collectibles in sometimes even harder-to-find classic secret rooms. Use your precision platforming skills to collect 'em all.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Rad Rodgers.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Rad Rodgers.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Rad Rodgers.png</marquee>
		<rating>4.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20161201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Interceptor Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>3D Realms</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shadowrun Returns.lnk</path>
		<name>Shadowrun Returns</name>
		<desc>Shadowrun Returns is a turn-based role-playing game with a skill based character progression system. You create your basic character and build the character based on your own needs during the game play, adding in the skills fit the most in your gamestyle. Combat is done with tactical, turn-based style, allowing you to take an advantage of your team skills as well as the surroundings of the battle. The game is played from an isometric view. The game world is created in a hand-painted style while the characters are in 3D.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Shadowrun Returns.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Shadowrun Returns.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Shadowrun Returns.png</marquee>
		<rating>3.88</rating>
		<releasedate>20130725T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Harebrained Schemes</developer>
		<publisher>Harebrained Schemes</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SiN Gold.lnk</path>
		<name>SiN Gold</name>
		<desc>When the CEO of SinTEK Industries begins injecting the streets with a DNA-altering drug, it's time to reassess the laws of morality. When the same twisted bio-chemist plans to overtake the world with her unholy army of genetically-engineered mutants, it's time to rewrite the golden rule. You are Colonel John R. Blade, head of the most prominent private protection agency in Freeport. Now Elexis Sinclaire is waging her holy war against the security industry...and you along with it. You've made a religion out of fighting crime. Now you're going to make Elexis pay for her sins. Updated Features * Added "Wages of SiN" expansion * Added modernized Steam master server support * Added and restored editing SDK * Added support for additional 16:9 video resolutions * Restored/uncensored various original game assets General Improvements * Optimizations to math, container types, and search algorithms * Restored support for *.sin pack files, re-packed assets * Removed obsolete IPX networking support * Restored original sound and music engine * Changed video format to open-source/patent-free OGV/Theora Fixes * Fixed crash in Docks cinematic * Fixed incorrect behavior in Thug AI * Fixed undefined camera position and occasional crash in Wages of SiN ending cinematic * r_palettemode cvar for software mode now reads and writes correct configuration variable * Fixed memory corruption issue during multiplayer initialization * cl_maxfps default changed to 200 to avoid issues with game running too fast * Repaired issue with extremely loud sounds on menu screens when FPS is too high * Fixed possible soft lock when using menu hotkeys while inside an in-game computer console * Restored missing assets for Beecadrone enemy</desc>
		<image>./mixart/SiN Gold.png</image>
		<video>./snap/SiN Gold.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/SiN Gold.png</marquee>
		<rating />
		<releasedate>19981031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>2015, Inc., Nightdive Studios, Ritual Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Activision, Nightdive Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Skybolt Zack.lnk</path>
		<name>Skybolt Zack</name>
		<desc>Skybolt Zack is a brand new fast-paced arcade gaming experience! With his Rocket Punches Zack leaps from enemy to enemy, destroying anything standing in his way!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Skybolt Zack.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Skybolt Zack.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Skybolt Zack.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>20191201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Devs Must Die</developer>
		<publisher>Green Man Gaming</publisher>
		<genre>Platformer</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Slain!.lnk</path>
		<name>Slain!</name>
		<desc>Slain: Back from Hell. A heavy metal inspired arcade combat with puzzle elements and gore galore. Stunning visuals and true old school gameplay accompanied by the most metal soundtrack you've ever heard.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Slain!.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Slain!.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Slain!.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>2016</releasedate>
		<developer>Steel Mantis</developer>
		<publisher>Digerati</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars - Rogue Squadron 3D.lnk</path>
		<name>Star Wars - Rogue Squadron 3D</name>
		<desc>Star Wars: Rogue Squadron (known as Star Wars: Rogue Squadron 3D on the PC) is an arcade-style action game co-developed by Factor 5 and LucasArts. The first of three games in the Rogue Squadron series, it was published by LucasArts and Nintendo and released for Windows and the Nintendo 64 in December 1998. Rogue Squadron was one of the first games to take advantage of the Nintendo 64's Expansion Pak, which allows gameplay at a 640 × 480 display resolution, instead of that system's standard 320 × 240 resolution. Set in the fictional Star Wars galaxy and inspired by the Star Wars: X-wing Rogue Squadron comics, the game takes place primarily between events in the films Star Wars and The Empire Strikes Back. The player controls Luke Skywalker, commander of the elite X-wing pilots known as Rogue Squadron. As the game progresses, Skywalker and Rogue Squadron fight the Galactic Empire in sixteen missions across various planets. Rogue Squadron received generally positive reviews. Critics praised the game's technical achievements and flight controls, but its use of distance fog and the lack of a multiplayer mode drew criticism. The game's sales exceeded expectations; by August 1999, more than one million copies had sold worldwide. It spawned two sequels developed and released for the Nintendo GameCube—Star Wars Rogue Squadron II: Rogue Leader and Star Wars Rogue Squadron III: Rebel Strike—as well as Star Wars: Episode I: Battle for Naboo, a spiritual successor released for Windows and Nintendo 64.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Star Wars - Rogue Squadron 3D.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Star Wars - Rogue Squadron 3D.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Star Wars - Rogue Squadron 3D.png</marquee>
		<rating>3.58</rating>
		<releasedate>19981207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Factor 5, LucasArts</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Flight Simulator</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars - TIE Fighter Collector's CD (1995).lnk</path>
		<name>Star Wars - TIE Fighter Collector's CD (1995)</name>
		<desc>The dark side beckons you on CD-ROM... Through their treachery on Yavin, the Alliance of rebels and other criminals has threatened the very foundation of the Empire. As an imperial navy starfighter pilot, your will safeguard imperiled lives throughout the galaxy. This compilation includes the campaigns from the original game Star Wars: TIE Fighter, the three campaigns from the add-on Star Wars: TIE Fighter - Defender of the Empire and also three new, never before released campaigns in a second add-on called Enemies of the Empire. In total there are more than 100 missions to fly and survive. In addition to the new missions, there are also some technical improvements to the game: Improved screen resolution to SVGA (640*480) Added new cut scenes Full voice mission briefings and radio calls (the so called "Talkie" version) Improved the interactive mission briefing</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Star Wars - TIE Fighter Collector's CD (1995).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Star Wars - TIE Fighter Collector's CD (1995).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Star Wars - TIE Fighter Collector's CD (1995).png</marquee>
		<rating>4.54</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts Entertainment Company LLC, Totally Games</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts Entertainment Company LLC</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Flight Simulator</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Stranger Things 3 - The Game.lnk</path>
		<name>Stranger Things 3 - The Game</name>
		<desc>Stranger Things 3: The Game is the official companion game to Season 3 of the hit original series! Play through familiar events from the series while also uncovering never-before-seen quests, character interactions, and secrets! This adventure game blends a distinctively retro art style with modern gameplay mechanics to deliver nostalgic fun with a fresh new twist. Just like in the show, teamwork is at the heart of Stranger Things 3: The Game. Fans can team up in two player local co-op to explore the world of Hawkins, solve puzzles, and battle the emerging evils of The Upside Down as one of twelve beloved characters from the show.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Stranger Things 3 - The Game.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Stranger Things 3 - The Game.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Stranger Things 3 - The Game.png</marquee>
		<rating>3.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20190704T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>BonusXP</developer>
		<publisher>BonusXP</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Moto Racer 3.lnk</path>
		<name>Moto Racer 3 Gold Edition</name>
		<desc>Moto Racer 3 is the third incarnation of this already classic motocycling game by Delphine Software. This time, you don't only race on famous circuits around the globe or let the mud fly with your Motocross cycle - there are even more styles to play: Racing on famous race track Motocross/Supercross in really muddy arenas Trial - drive your special motocycle on a obstacle-littered parcours without touching the floor or driving off the track in Freestyle, you can perform insane stunts in an arena full of ramps in Traffic mode, you drive in the streets of Paris - with traffic Everything is shown in rich 3D graphics with high detail.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Moto Racer 3.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Moto Racer 3.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Moto Racer 3.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20011201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Delphine Software</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./OutRun 2.lnk</path>
		<name>OutRun 2006 : Coast 2 Coast</name>
		<desc>OutRun 2006: Coast 2 Coast features 15 unique cars, the most ever seen in any OutRun game. In addition to the ten cars from OutRun 2 SP, new models include the 550 Barchetta, F355 Spider, Superamerica, 328 GTS, and the Ferrari F430. Some models cannot be unlocked on the PlayStation Portable or PlayStation 2 without the use of the cross-system connectivity feature inherent of the two systems.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/OutRun 2.png</image>
		<video>./snap/OutRun 2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/OutRun 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sumo Digital</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2-6</players>
		<md5>4b84e386e84d801224d0b1b733d7e66b</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shadow Warrior Classic Redux.lnk</path>
		<name>Shadow Warrior Classic Redux</name>
		<desc>Shadow Warrior Classic Redux is a PC version of Shadow Warrior, released on GOG.com - Challenging Steam achievements for only the most skilled warriors.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Shadow Warrior Classic Redux.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Shadow Warrior Classic Redux.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Shadow Warrior Classic Redux.png</marquee>
		<rating>3.27</rating>
		<releasedate>20130708T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>3D Realms, General Arcade, Level Infinity, Sunstorm Interactive, Wylde Productions</developer>
		<publisher>Devolver Digital, GT Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Skull Girls.lnk</path>
		<name>Skull Girls</name>
		<desc>Skullgirls is a beautiful, fast-paced, and critically acclaimed 2D fighting game that puts players in control of fierce warriors in an extraordinary Dark Deco world. Each of the 14 wildly original characters features unique gameplay mechanics and plenty of personality.

Skullgirls is the perfect fighting game for casual and competitive fighting game fans alike. Includes fully voiced story mode, gorgeous animation, and a soundtrack by Michiru Yamane.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Skull Girls.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Skullgirls.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Skull Girls.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20130822T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hidden Variable Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Autumn Games</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>c1382eeb2c50869900ea117bb8426a41</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yoku's Island Express.lnk</path>
		<name>Yoku's Island Express</name>
		<desc>Yoku has arrived on Mokumana and he’s ready for the easy life, soaking up the sun and delivering parcels on a tropical paradise! However, an ancient Island deity is trapped in a restless sleep - and it’s all down to Yoku to traverse the island using a unique blend of pinball mechanics, platforming and open world exploration, in an amazing adventure to help those in need!

Flip and bump our pint-sized protagonist around the stunning hand-painted island on your quest to rebuild the post-office, and wake an old god from its deep slumber.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Yokus Island Express.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Yokus Island Express.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Yokus Island Express.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20180529T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Villa Gorilla</developer>
		<publisher>Team17</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>5a8726bb01b99472bf92ba80c4103279</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dune 2000.lnk</path>
		<name>Dune 2000</name>
		<desc>Dune 2000 is a remake of the classic Dune II updated for Windows. In this Real-Time Strategy game, you can play one of the three houses, the evil Harkonnen, the greed filled Ordos or the noble Atreides.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Dune 2000.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Dune 2000.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dune 2000.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19981201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westwood Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battletoads.lnk</path>
		<name>Battletoads</name>
		<desc>The wait is over! Rash, Zitz and Pimple are returning at last to smash-hit their way through an all-new action-packed adventure of choreographed chaos, and couch co-op may never be the same again. 1-3 players will take control of the Battletoads and team up to storm through wild and unpredictable stages with only one rule – expect the unexpected. Teamwork makes the dream work in a drop-in, drop-out gameplay blast, filled with over-the-top gameplay moments that anyone can enjoy, but only a True ‘Toad’ can master.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Battletoads.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Battletoads.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Battletoads.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20201201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dlala Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>3</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Boulder Dash 30th Anniversary.lnk</path>
		<name>Boulder Dash 30th Anniversary</name>
		<desc>The original Boulder Dash® was created by Peter Liepa with Chris Gray over 30 years ago and published by First Star Software in 1984. Boulder Dash®-30th Anniversary™ is the first, and only, game in the multi-million unit selling Boulder Dash series to include both a world designed by Peter Liepa and another by Chris Gray.

Gem Collectors, Dig This! Boulder Dash-30th Anniversary finds our heroes, Rockford™, Crystal™ and others, facing a slew of new, exciting challenges in this legendary action puzzler. Dig through spectacular caves with 3D elements; avoid falling boulders; collect valuable gems and avoid nefarious enemies along the way as you search for the exit before time runs out. Discover treasure chests with rare collectibles, use potent power-ups. With 220 exciting levels across 11 new, gorgeous and unique worlds, and 10 playable characters, Boulder Dash-30th Anniversary is the best game in its 30 year history.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Boulder.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Boulder Dash.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Boulder.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20160914T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>BBG Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>BBG Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>72dc6506bc9f79183f3945e601139a7b</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Collin McRae Rally Remastered.lnk</path>
		<name>Collin McRae Rally Remastered</name>
		<desc>Colin McRae Rally features the car and track list from last year’s top selling mobile title and features THIRTY amazing rally stages in three environments taken from the PlayStation classic Colin McRae 2.0. for this PC and Mac edition. With a combined distance of over 130km, go flat out through the dirt and the dust of the Australian outback, take on dramatic climbs through the mountains of Greece and get sideways on the tight and twisty roads of Corsica.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/collin.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Collin Mcrae Rally.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Collin.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20140731T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codemasters</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>82f3e43dc7aaf9e2f9817543e224dc86</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Duck Tales.lnk</path>
		<name>Duck Tales Remastered</name>
		<desc>DuckTales: Remastered is a beautiful hand-crafted reimagining of one of the most cherished 8-bit titles of all time. Go back to one of the golden ages of gaming, now refined with a level of detail that will please the most hardened devoted Disney or retro Capcom fan alike.

Featuring hand-drawn animated sprites, authentic Disney character voices talent and richly painted level backgrounds from the classic cartoon TV series, Scrooge McDuck and family come to life like never before. The gameplay retains the authenticity of its 8-bit predecessor; simple and fun, with slight modifications to improve gameplay flow and design.

Embark on an authentic DuckTales adventure, as Scrooge McDuck and his three nephews Huey, Dewey and Louie travel to exotic locations throughout the world in their quest to retrieve the five Legendary Treasures.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ducktales.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Ducktales Remastered.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ducktales Remastered.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20130813T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>WayForward</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>d514500ad77e7f730884d8aa8f0a64ff</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Full Throttle Remastered.lnk</path>
		<name>Full Throttle Remastered</name>
		<desc>Originally released by LucasArts in 1995, Full Throttle is a classic graphic adventure game from industry legend Tim Schafer, telling the story of Ben Throttle; butt-kicking leader of biker gang the Polecats, who gets caught up in a tale of Motorcycles, Mayhem and Murder.

Now over 20 years later, Full Throttle is back in a remastered edition that features all new hand-drawn and 3D high-resolution artwork with 4k support, and with remastered audio and music. Blow your speakers with movie-quality sound and a full digital score featuring the GONE JACKALS - an authentic hard-hammerin' biker band!

Players will be able to switch back and forth between classic and remastered modes, and mix-n-match audio and graphics options to their heart’s desire. Also included is a concept art browser with work from Peter Chan, and a commentary track with the game’s original creators.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Full.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/full throttle.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/full.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20170418T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Double Fine Productions, Shiny Shoe</developer>
		<publisher>Double Fine Productions</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Point and Click</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>08c0c2fc74a3b15e55c17d854b0c265a</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ghostbusters Remastered.lnk</path>
		<name>Ghostbusters Remastered</name>
		<desc>The beloved and critically acclaimed Ghostbusters video game is back! Join the Ghostbusters team, fight monsters, capture ghosts, search for artifacts and have a blast destroying almost everything around you in this Remastered version of the third-person adventure Ghostbusters: The Video Game.

The single player campaign will put you through a story full of mystery and adventure. The authentic experience features the voices and in-game likenesses of Bill Murray, Dan Aykroyd, Harold Ramis, and Ernie Hudson in an original story penned by the writers of the original films - Dan Aykroyd and Harold Ramis. Test the team's mettle with large scale boss fights.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ghostbusters.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Ghostbusters.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ghostbusters.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20191004T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Saber Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Mad Dog Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>9262bc278429f5a8c230c81002f1f8cc</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Giana Sisters 2D.lnk</path>
		<name>Giana Sisters 2D</name>
		<desc>"The Great Giana Sisters" was one of the first platformers to be released on the Commodore 64. Although sales were stopped soon after the game’s release, The Great Giana Sisters became a cult classic, and Giana an iconic part of video game history.
In 2009, we started a reboot of Giana Sisters and released it on Nintendo DS. Giana Sisters DS marked the beginning of a new series of Giana Sisters games, with Giana Sisters: Twisted Dreams and Giana Sisters: Dream Runners being the latest releases.
Now we’re happy to give you a HD remake of the 2009 Nintendo DS version on Steam. It features beautiful HD graphics and full controller support. And of course the precise controls, intuitive handling and a smooth learning curve that platform fans expect. All balanced for hours of fun and challenges. It also contains the 32 levels of the original game – restored with love and care to resemble our take on the retro aesthetic.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Giana Sisters.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Giana Sisters 2D.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Giana Sisters.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20151023T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kasaa Solution</developer>
		<publisher>HandyGames, Black Forest Games</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>0a3fada15f00e6c3e777b4c7c8b77cdb</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Giana Sisters Dream Runners.lnk</path>
		<name>Giana Sisters Dream Runners</name>
		<desc>Race to the finish in Giana Sisters: Dream Runners, a fast-paced, head-to-head platformer for up to four players.

Run and jump, dash and smash, daze and teleport, morph and cannon… oh you get the idea: mess with your opponents!

The game pits up to four players (or AI opponents) against each other in local and online competition, speed-running for the finish in an effort to push each other off the screen with the help of boosters and power-ups.
Switch the level layout on the fly as you rush through dreamgates. Collect gems to fill your speed booster and use your power-ups to knock out the other players and claim victory!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/gsdr.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Gsdr.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Gsdr.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20150826T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Black Forest Games</developer>
		<publisher>EuroVideo Medien</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>d75e3ebdecf9d99c807d31db776b5b5e</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Giana Sisters Rise of the Owlverlord.lnk</path>
		<name>Giana Sisters Rise of the Owlverlord</name>
		<desc>Giana Sisters: Twisted Dreams - Rise of the Owlverlord is a blistering platformer with morphing worlds, featuring seven brand new levels, a new boss and new gripping tracks from Chris Hülsbeck and Machinae Supremacy!

Dash through tricky levels and transform the whole world at will in this fast-paced platformer. Rise of the Owlverlord combines graphics that pack a visual punch and tight controls with the challenge of retro era platforming. Fluidly morph between two dynamically different dream worlds to solve puzzles and combat grueling enemies and bosses. You’ll have to intertwine perky Giana's twirling jump with punky Giana's hammering dash attack to survive her dual nightmare.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/owlverlord.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/owlverlord.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Owlverlord.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20130926T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Black Forest Games</developer>
		<publisher>HandyGames, Black Forest Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>52b105756f88e5cffea3c8ce79bce477</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Giana Sisters Twisted Dreams.lnk</path>
		<name>Giana Sisters Twisted Dreams</name>
		<desc>Giana Sisters: Twisted Dreams is a blistering hardcore platformer with contrasting worlds. Warp Giana’s vivid dreams to alter your abilities and destroy the twisted creatures lurking within. Giana Sisters: Twisted Dreams combines the challenge of retro era platforming with graphics that pack a visual punch and tight controls.

Fluidly morph between two dynamically different dream worlds to solve puzzles and combat grueling enemies. Players will have to intertwine sweet Giana's twirling jump attack with Punk Giana's hammering dash attack to survive the dualling dimensions.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/twisted.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/twisted dreams.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/twisted.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20121023T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Black Forest Games</developer>
		<publisher>HandyGames, Black Forest Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>bb13fd479ae964b124a3667a50486834</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grandia 2 Anniversary.lnk</path>
		<name>Grandia 2 Anniversary</name>
		<desc>Take on the role of a hardened mercenary with a heart and go on an epic adventure filled with magic, new friendships, and surprising storyline twists in search of a weapon once wielded by a deity. Experience the classic tale of a band of adventurers destined to save the world, but things are not always as they seem...</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Grandia 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Grandia II.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Grandia 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20150824T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>GAME ARTS, Sickhead Games</developer>
		<publisher>GungHo Online Entertainment America</publisher>
		<genre>RPG</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>703e2cab8b542777dc01e45400b692d2</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grandia HD Remaster.lnk</path>
		<name>Grandia HD Remaster</name>
		<desc>GRANDIA tells the story of Justin, the protagonist, and his companions in a race against the evil Garlyle Forces to uncover the long-lost secrets of an ancient civilization. Experience the game that became an instant classic and is considered to be one of the most influential RPGs of all time.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Grandia.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Grandia HD Remaster.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Grandia.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20191015T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>GAME ARTS, Sickhead Games</developer>
		<publisher>GungHo Online Entertainment America</publisher>
		<genre>RPG</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>4bb84ff37e3f3f9ef308dff1daedde18</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grim Fandango Remastered.lnk</path>
		<name>Grim Fandango Remastered</name>
		<desc>One of the most acclaimed adventure games of all time is now back, better than ever. Grim Fandango's epic story of four years in the life (or death) of Manny Calavera, travel agent to the dead, has been remastered to look, sound, and control even better than when it won GameSpot's Game of the Year award upon its original launch. Grim Fandango still stands as a classic of the genre, with unforgettable characters and unique combination of film noir and Mexican folklore.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Grim.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Grim Fandango.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Grim.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20150127T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Double Fine Productions, Shiny Shoe</developer>
		<publisher>Double Fine Productions</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Point and Click</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>46c2dcd4d07a60f3a341dc9985dd675a</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Guilty Gear Xrd Revelator.lnk</path>
		<name>Guilty Gear Xrd Revelator</name>
		<desc>Carrying on the legacy from 1998, comes the next addition to the "Guilty Gear" series! All visuals have been tweaked to the finest detail and hand-polished by the animation masters to produce the top quality hand-drawn anime effect! Game contents revamped to provide for gamers of all skill levels, you cannot miss out on this one!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/revelator.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/GG Revelator.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Revelator.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20161216T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arc System Works</developer>
		<publisher>Arc System Works</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>e782b635af0c57e21ab6bef0c5e3cc86</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Guilty Gear Xrd Sign.lnk</path>
		<name>Guilty Gear Xrd Sign</name>
		<desc>Revolutionary graphics, Overwhelming battle system!
Carrying on the legacy from 1998, comes the newest addition to the "Guilty Gear" series! All visuals, especially the characters, have been redrawn in full 3D, tweaked to the finest detail and hand-polished by the animation masters to produce the top quality hand-drawn anime effect!

The game's battle system has also been revamped, with a central emphasis on it's core system, "Roman Cancel"! Devise your own game plan with this new system, and craft your own battle strategy!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/sign.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/gg sign.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sign.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20151209T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arc System Works</developer>
		<publisher>Arc System Works</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>91caec8d61e0764d4ab765a6ae7485ad</md5>
	</game>
	<game id="156369">
		<path>./Dott.lnk</path>
		<name>Maniac Mansion 2 : Day of the Tentacle</name>
		<desc>Purple Tentacle, one of the crazy Dr. Fred's creations, drinks contaminated water from Dr. Fred's Sludge-o-matic. He mutates into an insane genius and grows arms, and now he's plotting to take over the world. In an effort to stop him, Dr. Fred sends three friends, Bernard, Hoagie and Laverne back in time to yesterday, in order for them to turn off the Sludge-o-matic and stop the sludge from spilling into the river, thus preventing the whole incident. Naturally, the cheap doctor uses a fake diamond over a real one in his time machine, which blows up sending Hoagie 200 years into the past and Laverne 200 years into the future.

Now you must bring back Hoagie and Laverne, with the help of the time machine's ability to move objects between time periods, and then stop evil Purple from taking over the world.

Day of the Tentacle is a point-and-click adventure game and a sequel to Maniac Mansion. The player controls Bernard, and later also Hoagie and Laverne, being able to switch between them at any time. By using the commands at the bottom of the screen, the character can pick up items, use them on other things, talk to people and more. Any of the three friends can also send his items across time to another friend. 

The game takes place in the same building, but in three different eras, and thus affecting history takes a vital part in some puzzles. For instance, Hoagie can hide a bottle of wine in the XVIIIth century, and Laverne discovers the bottle in the XXIIIth century - but by then, the wine has already turned into vinegar.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Dott.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Dott.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dott.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Point and Click</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>5ab5533b80f529070c110691733f61ec</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Kay Anniversary.lnk</path>
		<name>Legend of Kay Anniversary</name>
		<desc>10 years after its initial release, Legend of Kay - Anniversary is a thoroughly remastered version of the original game: high-resolution textures; new, more detailed character models; modern rendering techniques and crystal-clear surround sound give this great classic a new shine.

Full of fond allusions to old martial arts films and pop culture quotes, Legend of Kay - Anniversary is both an incredibly funny game and a challenging action-adventure for young and old alike.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Kay.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Legend of Kay.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Kay.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20150727T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>KAIKO, Neon Studios</developer>
		<publisher>THQ Nordic</publisher>
		<genre>RPG</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>b4dd5ed76f4fe66a03e0241baafc5089</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Monkey Island 2.lnk</path>
		<name>Monkey Island 2 Special Edition</name>
		<desc>Wannabe pirate Guybrush Threepwood, and the now zombie pirate LeChuck, return in what has long been considered one of the greatest LucasArts adventure games of all time.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Monkey Island 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Monkey Island 2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Monkey Island 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20100707T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Lucas Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Lucas Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>0ca97be26865b09f0c6136bfe8cb87ea</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Monkey Island.lnk</path>
		<name>Monkey Island Special Edition</name>
		<desc>The games follow the misadventures of the hapless Guybrush Threepwood as he struggles to become the most notorious pirate in the Caribbean, defeat the plans of the evil undead pirate LeChuck and win the heart of governess Elaine Marley.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Monkey Island.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Monkey Island.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Monkey Island.png</marquee>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20100307T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Lucas Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Lucas Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>1e8f237a077fa21653af7eff3fd19404</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./PAC-MAN and the Ghostly Adventures.lnk</path>
		<name>PAC-MAN and the Ghostly Adventures</name>
		<desc>Pac is back in an all-new experience for a whole new generation of fans. Featuring an original storyline inspired by the show as well as all the charming characters from the highly anticipated PAC-MAN and the Ghostly Adventures animated series created and produced by Avi Arad, acclaimed director and founder of Marvel Studios.

Pac and his 2 best friends, Spiral and Cylindria, rise to the challenge of protecting their home, all the while fighting for: Friendship, Freedom and the Future!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/pac.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Pac-man.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/pac.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20131029T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco Bandai Games</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Arcade</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>b426c2452a5f910e51df71ba379dbd8a</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Panzer Dragoon Remake.lnk</path>
		<name>Panzer Dragoon Remake</name>
		<desc>A new, remade version of the Panzer Dragoon game – true to the original, with improved graphics and controls, that suit modern gaming standards! On a far, lone planet, you encounter two dragons awaken from the ancient times. Armed with a deadly gun from the past, and the guidance of your armored blue dragon, you must fulfill your destiny and keep the Prototype Dragon from reaching the Tower or die trying.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/panzer.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Panzer.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/panzer.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20200925T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>MegaPixel Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Forever Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>36066b63a3b1f638275bb30c08a70aa3</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Praetorians HD Remaster.lnk</path>
		<name>Praetorians HD Remaster</name>
		<desc>Praetorians is set amidst the political machinations of an emerging Roman Empire. Prove your worth on the battlefields of Egypt, the combat theaters of Gaul and finally the heart of the Empire itself in Italy, in the crusade to become Emperor.

Your quest will not be an easy one, as the Empire is heavily defended by thousands of different troop types and war machines, all with special skills and individual strengths. To emerge victorious, you’ll need to learn to combine your units and exploit the weaknesses of your enemies. But beware – the closer you get to the Emperor, the closer you get to facing the Praetorian Guard – the most powerful and deadly fighting force in the Empire!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Praetorians.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Praetorians.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Praetorians.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Torus Games, Pyro Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Kalypso Medias</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>584b634f0c86a176782a5bda209f286d</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rocketron.lnk</path>
		<name>Rocketron</name>
		<desc>Fly through the sky! Rain down fire on the enemy forces from above! Enjoy solid combat and simple non-linear exploration in this high flying side-scrolling action shooter!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Rocketron.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Rocketron.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Rocketron.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>2020</releasedate>
		<developer>Astro Port</developer>
		<publisher>Henteko Doujin</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sam and Max.lnk</path>
		<name>Sam and Max Remastered</name>
		<desc>With enhanced graphics, new widescreen and gamepad support, five new musical tracks, and the same brain-tickling puzzles and offbeat humor that won it IGN's Best Adventure GOTY award back in the day, Sam &amp; Max Save the World Remastered is a modern classic that you'll love to play—or play agai</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Sam Max.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Sam Max.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sam Max.png</marquee>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20200312T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Skunkape Games</developer>
		<publisher>Skunkape Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<md5>5d242ced5a9c10557ec71c40013ff3c6</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SEGA Rally.lnk</path>
		<name>SEGA Rally</name>
		<desc>At an incredible 30 frames a second AM#3 delivers the most gruelling driving experience yet! Skill and technique are essential as one or two players navigate their way around four courses of the most arduous terrain ever to soil your living room carpet!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Sega Rally.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/sega Rally.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sega Rally.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19970131T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>990ac8e5ade8ede89eb159ed323d9b81</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Settlers 2 10th Anniversary.lnk</path>
		<name>Settlers 2 10th Anniversary</name>
		<desc>After fighting a losing battle with drought and the mysterious disappearance of their women, a brave people set out to sea. The survivors need your help as they are challenged to the ultimate test: survival. Food and building materials must be developed, for the productivity of future shipbuilders, foresters, brewers, and scouts depends on it. Construct gold, coal, iron, and granite mines. Cultivate the land, build farms, establish fisheries and hunting grounds, build up your stocks of animals and manage forests; the well-being of your subjects rests in your hands. Most important is to get your women back!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Settlers 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Settlers 2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Settlers 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.70</rating>
		<releasedate>20061026T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Blue Byte Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>1ef564be16ed2a20e9ea963d481deb56</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shadow Complex.lnk</path>
		<name>Shadow Complex</name>
		<desc>Powered by Unreal Engine technology, the “modern and masterful side-scroller” Shadow Complex became an instant classic when initially released in 2009, exclusively for Xbox 360. The fan favorite won more than 50 Game of the Year and Editor’s Choice Awards and was one of the most popular console games of the year. Shadow Complex Remastered features all the great content from the original game updated with exciting new enhancements and achievements.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Shadow.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Shadow Complex.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/shadow.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20160503T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>chAIR Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Epic Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>6aa376731b9bb2d15ebe0db8ec8fb12a</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Mania.lnk</path>
		<name>Sonic Mania</name>
		<desc>The ultimate celebration of past and future. An all-new adventure with Sonic, Tails and Knuckles full of unique bosses, rolling 2D landscapes and fun classic gameplay. Sonic Mania bring retro fast-paced platforming into the future through pixel perfect 2D graphics runnimg at 60FPS.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Sonic Mania.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Sonic Mania.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sonic Mania.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20170829T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Christian Whitehead, Headcannon, PagodaWest Games</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>b93360e11de682d704ae64b6db710a61</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spyro Reignited Trilogy.lnk</path>
		<name>Spyro Reignited Trilogy</name>
		<desc>The original roast master is back! Same sick burns, same smoldering attitude, now all scaled up in stunning HD. Spyro is bringing the heat like never before in the Spyro™ Reignited Trilogy game collection. Rekindle the fire with the original three games, Spyro™ the Dragon, Spyro™ 2: Ripto's Rage! and Spyro™: Year of the Dragon. Explore the expansive realms, re-encounter the fiery personalities and relive the adventure in fully remastered glory. Because when there’s a realm that needs saving, there’s only one dragon to call.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/spyro.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Spyro.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/spyro.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20190903T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Toys For Bob, Iron Galaxy</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>0967674e881fe52f0826617e5673051a</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Fighter 30th Anniversary Collection.lnk</path>
		<name>Street Fighter 30th Anniversary Collection</name>
		<desc>Celebrate Street Fighter’s historic legacy with the Street Fighter 30th Anniversary Collection. In this massive collection of 12 Street Fighter titles, perfect arcade balance makes it to consoles and PC for the first time ever. Four groundbreaking titles let you hop online and relive the arcade experience through the online Arcade Mode or play with friends - SFII Hyper Fighting, Super SFII Turbo, SF Alpha 3 and SFIII: Third Strike!!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Street Fighter 30th.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Street Fighter 30th.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Street Fighter 30th.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20180529T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Eclipse</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>e79f46038eead9bd5dec2678f8fc241f</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Bomberman R.lnk</path>
		<name>Super Bomberman R</name>
		<desc>Play alone or with a friend in a Story Mode jam-packed with different levels. Re-experience classic Battle Mode, or discover the brand new Grand Prix Mode in which team play is just as important as individual skills! New characters are joining the fight. Play locally or online with friends and players from around the world! Super Bomberman R is the biggest Bomberman game ever!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Super Bomberman R.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Super Bomberman R.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./Wheel/Super Bomberman R.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20180612T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>1323cb6c5e998d9773f5fc0f76ddcb8d</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Luckys Tale.lnk</path>
		<name>Super Luckys Tale</name>
		<desc>Super Lucky’s Tale is a delightful, playground platformer for all ages that follows Lucky, the ever-optimistic, energetic, and lovable hero, on his quest to find his inner strength and help his sister rescue the Book of Ages from Jinx. Jinx is the scheming and mysterious villain trying to reshape the world, but for what reason?

Along the way, encounter a hilarious supporting cast of friends and adversaries. Lucky must confront the nefarious Kitty Litter, Jinx's mischievous kids - self-taught villains who might not be getting Jinx's plans quite right. Lucky meets friends and allies along the way too. He meets misplaced Yetis, Kookie Spookies, a village of farming worms, and other colorful friends inhabiting the Book of Ages.

Test your skills with puzzles and nerve-wracking obstacle courses. Explore hidden secrets of new worlds with Lucky's signature burrow move. Dive into unpredictable foxholes, or try devilish side scrolling challenge levels to unlock additional rewards.

Head back to the era of classic platformers with challenges players of all skill levels and all ages can enjoy.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Super Luckys Tale.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Lucky.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Super Luckys Tale.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20180914T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Playful Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>XBOX Game Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>df0c65ec0efc07b6c0eae5ea9d9c70c2</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Monkey Ball Banana Blitz HD Remake.lnk</path>
		<name>Super Monkey Ball Banana Blitz HD Remake</name>
		<desc>Hold onto your bananas, because Super Monkey Ball: Banana Blitz HD is rolling your way!Head back into the fantastical world of Super Monkey Ball and blast through 100 twisting and turning levels. Play as one of your favorite monkeys and take back your bananas from the space alien pirate king, Captain Crabuchin. For the first time ever, play as Sonic the Hedgehog and dash through the levels, and unlock a selection of costumes for every monkey in the base game.

Challenge your friends and family to 10 fan-favourite Party Games! Feeling like the fastest, most manoeuvrable monkey around? Try out Time Attack mode or the gruelling Decathlon endurance run! Will you make it onto the online leaderboards?</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Super Monkey Ball.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Super Monkey Ball.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Super Monkey Ball.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20191210T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>6c449cbc38f992a628cf777b5505ba19</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Swine HD Remaster.lnk</path>
		<name>Swine HD Remaster</name>
		<desc>The S.W.I.N.E. HD Remaster is a unique edition of the remastered original game. You will not only receive the complete HD remastered version of S.W.I.N.E. improved with all the patches since its release, but you will also get three exclusive bonuses.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Swine.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/swine.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Swine.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20190523T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kite Games</developer>
		<publisher>Assemble Entertainment, WhisperGames</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>1e69444afbc3413f509650a848c35dc2</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Team Sonic Racing.lnk</path>
		<name>Team Sonic Racing</name>
		<desc>Team Sonic Racing combines the best elements of arcade and fast-paced competitive style racing as you face-off with friends in intense multiplayer racing. Race together and work together as a team by sharing power-ups and speed boosts. Take control of your racing style - Choose from 3 distinct character types and unlock game changing vehicle customization options to suit your racing style.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Team Sonic Racing.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Team Sonic Racing.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./Wheel/Team Sonic Racing.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20190521T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sumo Digital</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>e3ef3e0ccca2133b19c140734e625f15</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wonderboy Dragons Trap.lnk</path>
		<name>Wonderboy Dragons Trap</name>
		<desc>Boasting beautiful, hand-drawn animations and a re-orchestrated soundtrack, the cult classic returns with a unique blend of exploration, action, and adventure! Cursed into a half-human, half-lizard monstrosity by the Meka-Dragon, you are in search for a cure! The only way you can return to human form is to find the Salamander Cross, a magical item with the power to remove curses...</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Wonder Boy The Dragons Trap.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Wonderboy.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Wonderboy Dragons Trap.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20170608T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Lizardcube</developer>
		<publisher>Dotemu</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>127f2d1219b3ac797837e2a51038203e</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jets'n'Guns 2.lnk</path>
		<name>Jets'n'Guns 2</name>
		<desc>Jets'n'Guns 2 is a side-scrolling space shooter with insane levels of action and destruction. Now with local co-op support! The universe is once again facing a terrible threat. An unknown but powerful entity from another dimension has entered our reality and is attempting to wipe out all sentient life. The inhabited planets of the galaxy are too divided to take action. It's up to you, the bravest and finest pilot in the galaxy, to face the enemy alone and prevail against overwhelming odds! Assume the role of an elite space pilot and jump into an epic adventure to save the universe from inevitable doom. Travel the galaxies and unleash an arsenal of the deadliest weapons and devices ever installed in a spaceship!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Jets'n'Guns 2.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Jets'n'Guns 2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Jets'n'Guns 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20201201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rake in Grass</developer>
		<publisher>Rake in Grass</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Abes Oddysee New N Tasty.lnk</path>
		<name>Abes Oddysee New N Tasty</name>
		<desc>Abe's back, and the original hero's about to face his oddest challenge yet!A mudokon chosen by the fickle finger of fate, Abe was a first class Floor-Waxer for RuptureFarms who was catapulted into a life of adventure.Late one night he overheard plans from his boss, Molluck the Glukkon, to turn Abe and his fellow Mudokons into Tasty Treats as a final effort to rescue Molluck's failing meatpacking empire!Can Abe change the fate of thousands and rescue the Mudokons? Can he escape the dark recesses of RuptureFarms and the desolate, uninviting, and downright terrifying surrounding environment?Lead our unlikely hero on his mission because if he doesn’t make it… Abe’s back on the menu!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/abes.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Oddworld.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/abes.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20150225T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Just Add Water</developer>
		<publisher>Oddworld Inhabitants</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>3f13089061918c327af118bbe881c1aa</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Black Mesa.lnk</path>
		<name>Black Mesa Definitive Edition</name>
		<desc>Black Mesa is a first-person shooter video game, developed and published by Crowbar Collective. It is a third-party remake of Half-Life (1998) in the Source game engine. Originally published as a free mod in September 2012, the game was given approval by Valve (the developers of Half-Life) for a commercial release. The commercial version was first published as an early access title in May 2015 and had its full release in March 2020 for Microsoft Windows and Linux.

Black Mesa was developed in response to Half-Life: Source (2005), Valve's port of Half-Life to the Source engine, which lacked new features or improvements. The project was formed by the merging of two separate teams that wanted to improve on the Source remake, eventually becoming Crowbar Collective. While they had originally targeted a release by 2009, the team realized they had rushed to this point, and reevaluated their efforts to improve the quality of the remake.

Since then, attention to details, adapting the game to an improved version of the Source engine, and completely reworking the oft-derided final chapters of Half-Life known as Xen had lengthened the development efforts into the remake. Due to its long development time, the modification became notable for its delays on the status of its completion. Among major changes in the remake include reskinned collection of textures, models, and NPCs; a longer runtime; improved level and puzzle design along with challenging enemy artificial intelligence, and additional dialogue and story elements.

Black Mesa received positive reviews upon its initial release and was lauded as the game was updated and improved. Praise was directed towards the gameplay and attention to detail, comparing it to that of an official Valve release, as well as for the improvements they had made on the Xen chapters.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Black Mesa.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Black Mesa.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Black Mesa.png</marquee>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20200603T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crowbar Collective</developer>
		<publisher>Crowbar Collective</publisher>
		<genre>First-Person Shooter</genre>
		<md5>cfb28f8fbb79bb2812812a6344e9a5a2</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bloo Kid 2.lnk</path>
		<name>Bloo Kid 2</name>
		<desc>Bloo Kid 2 is a classic 2D retro-style platformer experience with lovely designed pixel-graphics and a full chiptune soundtrack. Run, jump and swim your way through five huge worlds with twelve levels each. Master brutal bossfights and discover lots of secrets in the world of Bloo Kid 2.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Bloo Kid 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Bloo Kid 2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Bloo Kid 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20140306T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>winterworks</developer>
		<publisher>winterworks</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>a3450d4ea5819448cf2b411fe27356b2</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Outrun 2.lnk</path>
		<name>OutRun 2006: Coast 2 Coast</name>
		<desc>OutRun 2006: Coast 2 Coast is a racing game developed by Sumo Digital and published by Sega for the Xbox, PlayStation 2, PlayStation Portable and Windows PC. It is chiefly based upon OutRun 2 SP (which itself received a Japanese-only PS2 port), with the addition of five new cars (two of which are from OutRun 2 on the Xbox), rebalanced and added features and a "Coast 2 Coast" mode.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Outrun 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Outrun 2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Outrun 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20060630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sumo Digital Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<md5>afd42f99dee1886e93165de8fa172054</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yooka-Laylee and the Impossible Lair.lnk</path>
		<name>Yooka-Laylee and the Impossible Lair</name>
		<desc>Yooka-Laylee and the Impossible Lair is a brand-new 2.5D platformer from some of the key creative talent behind 'Donkey Kong Country'. With their arch-nemesis Capital B up to no good, the buddy duo needs to spring into action once again to save the day. To thwart his evil plan of using a “Hivemind” device to enslave an entire kingdom of bees, our heroes need to take the fight to Capital B’s “Impossible” Lair. Things look tough, but with the help of Queen Phoebee and her Royal Beetallion , Yooka and Laylee might just have a chance!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/yooka.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/yooka.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/yooka.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20191008T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Playtonic Games</developer>
		<publisher>Team17</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<md5>b329c5cd2a9bcba409c1425a2772c417</md5>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Child of Light.lnk</path>
		<name>Child of Light</name>
		<desc>The kingdom of Lemuria is in despair The Black Queen has stolen the Sun, the Moon and the Stars. You play as Aurora, a young princess with a pure heart whose soul is brought to the kingdom of Lemuria. Embark on a quest to recapture the three sources of light, defeat the Black Queen and restore the kingdom of Lemuria.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Child of Light.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Child of Light.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Child of Light.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20140430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft Montreal</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>c90f3853868b013c4c672293f87748f8</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Deep Rock Galactic.lnk</path>
		<name>Deep Rock Galactic</name>
		<desc>Deep Rock Galactic is a 4-player sci-fi co-op shooter taking place in procedurally generated and 100% destructible caves on an extremely hostile alien planet.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Deep Rock Galactic.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Deep Rock Galactic.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Deep Rock Galactic.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20180821T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ghost Ship Games</developer>
		<publisher>Coffee Stain Publishing</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Duke Nukem 3D 20th Anniversary World Tour.lnk</path>
		<name>Duke Nukem 3D 20th Anniversary World Tour</name>
		<desc>Frag like it’s 1996 – this time with even more asses to kick! Join the world’s greatest action hero in Duke Nukem 3D: 20th Anniversary World Tour as he saves Earth once again, kicking alien ass and saving babes across the globe along the way.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Duke.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Duke.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Duke.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nerve Software, Gearbox Software</developer>
		<publisher>Gearbox Publishing</publisher>
		<md5>3b052e445673f60e166bb272e41000d6</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man 11.lnk</path>
		<name>Mega Man 11</name>
		<desc>Thirty years ago, in 1987, a super robot named Mega Man was created. In 2018 after 30 years of unforgettable adventures the fight for everlasting peace continues! The tight action-platformer gameplay that made the series a success is alive and well. To save the day, the Blue Bomber must battle Robot Masters and take their powerful weapons for himself, which now changes the hero's appearance with new levels of detail. A new, vivid visual style refreshes the series' iconic colorfulness, combining hand-drawn environments with detailed, 3D character models.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Mega Man.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Mega Man 11.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Mega Man 11.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20181002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>a78253bf0823c76941dcbc22c1232ed0</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Monkey Barrels.lnk</path>
		<name>Monkey Barrels</name>
		<desc>The Monkey-Crab War to end all wars begins! It's monkeys vs. machines in this zany action-packed shooter! In a world ruled by the consumer electronics giant Crabbenwold Electro, a pair of brave monkeys set out on a journey to rescue their kidnapped friends from an evil army of robot appliances! In addition to a 22-stage story mode, there's also an online competitive mode! Features 3D pixel art that puts a fresh spin on old-school graphics! Tons of fun and challenging stages await you!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Monkey Barrels.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Monkey Barrels.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Monkey Barrels.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20190821T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Good-Feel</developer>
		<publisher>Good-Feel</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>6</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Monster Boy and the Cursed Kingdom.lnk</path>
		<name>Monster Boy and the Cursed Kingdom</name>
		<desc>A legendary game series returns with an all-new adventure and in stunning HD! Monster Boy is a colorful side-scrolling action adventure created in cooperation with Ryuichi Nishizawa, the creator of the famous Wonder Boy in Monster World series. Monster Boy is being created to bring back the enjoyment of the classic games that shine by simplicity. Exciting gameplay, upbeat music and smooth graphics. You'll need to overcome huge bosses, find hidden passages, discover powerful equipment and use all your wits and skills to remove a powerful curse. Transform into 6 different creatures, each with their own skills and abilities. Take advantage of all the unique powers to open new paths and advance in an epic story. We put all our passion into Monster Boy to create a truly enjoyable love letter to gaming from the 80's and 90's - will you join us and celebrate together with us?

Features:
* Switch between up to 6 playable characters: Each character feels different and all of them keep the gameplay fresh and exciting.
* Unlock new paths and secrets with special equipment: Look for magic weapons and equipment that gradually open up the world.
* Over 15 hours of epic adventure: Explore the new 'Monster World' in a huge interconnected environment.
* Soundtrack from Japanese superstar composers: Yuzo Koshiro, Motoi Sakuraba, Michiru Yamane, Keiki Kobayashi and Takeshi Yanagawa</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Monster.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Monster.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Monster.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20190725T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>FDG Entertainment GmbH &amp; Co.KG</developer>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>ac0390eb723c7c557db5fb8d27b5a6c0</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Morbid - The Seven Acolytes.lnk</path>
		<name>Morbid - The Seven Acolytes</name>
		<desc>Morbid: The Seven Acolytes is a Horrorpunk Action RPG filled with Lovecraftian horrors and Cronenbergian gore, making it the most gruesome take on the isometric Souls-like genre yet! You are the last surviving Striver of Dibrom. Your duty, for which you have trained your whole life, is to defeat the Seven Acolytes, accursed and powerful beings, possessed by malevolent deities called Gahars. Challenging foes, mini-bosses, and memorable large-scale boss fights with fully orchestrated music, are central to the world of Morbid. To overcome these obstacles you must master the combat, as well as improve your character and gear through a wealth of elements such as Quests, Perks, Runes, Upgrades, and Looting. The Gahars have bound their twisted minds to the flesh of the Seven Acolytes, for without hosts they cannot survive. You must slay the Acolytes, thus ridding the Gahars of their flesh. Succeed, and you'll free the kingdom from the heavy yoke of their terror. Fail, and the malicious gods rule on, as the Acolytes rise anew, and madness prevails.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Morbid - The Seven Acolytes.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Morbid - The Seven Acolytes.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Morbid - The Seven Acolytes.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20200821T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Still Running</developer>
		<publisher>Merge Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Natsuki Chronicles.lnk</path>
		<name>Natsuki Chronicles</name>
		<desc>New dramatic horizontal shoot ’em up that takes place in the same setting as Ginga Force. An immersive story that follows protagonist Natsuki. Discover the story of her past as a rookie pilot up to present day with events that are parallel to those in Ginga Force.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Natsuki Chronicles.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Natsuki Chronicles.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Natsuki Chronicles.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20210821T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Qute</developer>
		<publisher>Rising Star Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ori and the Blind Forest Definitive Edition.lnk</path>
		<name>Ori and the Blind Forest: Definitive Edition</name>
		<desc>“Ori and the Blind Forest” tells the tale of a young orphan destined for heroics, through a visually stunning Action-Platformer crafted by Moon Studios.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Blind.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Blind Forest.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Blind.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20160427T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Moon Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>a06fd3412361199e7e17c7698abbd5bc</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ori and the Will of Wisps.lnk</path>
		<name>Ori and the Will of the Wisps</name>
		<desc>Players assume control of Ori, a white guardian spirit. To progress in the game, players are tasked to move between platforms and solve puzzles. Similarly to The Blind Forest, Will of the Wisps is expected to feature a system called "soul links", which allows players to save at will, and an upgrade system that gives players the ability to strengthen Ori's skills. The game world unfolds to the player in the fashion of a Metroidvania, with new abilities allowing the player to access previously inaccessible areas. Some of the foundational gameplay elements were inspired by the Rayman and Metroid franchises.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Will.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/will of wisps.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Will.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20200311T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Moon Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>c5e891fcb81fdc89a1b96774be89f8a8</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Puyo Puyo Tetris 2.lnk</path>
		<name>Puyo Puyo Tetris 2</name>
		<desc>What happens when two classic puzzle games collide? Culture shock, and lots of it! That's what the characters of the Puyo Puyo series find themselves in when a whole host of crazy characters claiming to be Tetris masters crash into the Puyoverse. And it's not only Tetris they want to play - they also claim to be pretty good at Puyo popping! Can these two brainteasers co-exist without driving each other crazy?

Puyo Puyo Tetris is a combination of the Puyo Puyo and Tetris series in which the player battles through seven chapters of 10 stages each, playing as a total of 26 characters in the hopes of determining which puzzle game series is the better of the two. As usual, the objective is to score chains and drown opponents in a wave of Nuisance Puyos and/or extra blocks. But the rules change every time - one match might have the player(s) swapping between Puyo Puyo and Tetris fields, while another may allow them to use items to hinder opponents' progress. Also, at certain points, the player will encounter challenges, where the objective is to reach a certain goal before time runs out.

The traditional battle mode is of course still intact, with up to 4 players battling for Puyo (or Tetris, or who knows? Maybe both) bragging rights.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Tetris 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Tetris 2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tetris 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>O-Two, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<md5>f50bda705e4d27609bdd12e59b901a55</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Puyo Puyo Tetris.lnk</path>
		<name>Puyo Puyo Tetris</name>
		<desc>Two puzzle game juggernauts collide as Tetris®, one of the largest-selling and recognized brands in gaming history, and Puyo Puyo™ from SEGA combine to create a fun-to-play, fast-paced, competitive party game like no other! There’s a ton of different styles of gameplay – from the single-player Adventure and Challenge modes to the ferocious competition of the up-to-four-player Arcade modes. Unlock new characters and backgrounds in Adventure mode, or unlock new character voices, skins for Puyos and Tetriminos, backgrounds and more in the in-game Shop. You can even try your puzzle skills on a global scale by playing any of the multiplayer modes with up to four players online in Puzzle League or Free Play modes.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/puyo.png</image>
		<video>./snap/puyo puyo tetris.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/puyo.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20180227T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team, Bitbaboon</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<md5>7a6220bfeb9995ba259309c172c96887</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ray's The Dead.lnk</path>
		<name>Ray's The Dead</name>
		<desc>Morbid: The Seven Acolytes is a Horrorpunk Action RPG filled with Lovecraftian horrors and Cronenbergian gore, making it the most gruesome take on the isometric Souls-like genre yet! You are the last surviving Striver of Dibrom. Your duty, for which you have trained your whole life, is to defeat the Seven Acolytes, accursed and powerful beings, possessed by malevolent deities called Gahars. Challenging foes, mini-bosses, and memorable large-scale boss fights with fully orchestrated music, are central to the world of Morbid. To overcome these obstacles you must master the combat, as well as improve your character and gear through a wealth of elements such as Quests, Perks, Runes, Upgrades, and Looting. The Gahars have bound their twisted minds to the flesh of the Seven Acolytes, for without hosts they cannot survive. You must slay the Acolytes, thus ridding the Gahars of their flesh. Succeed, and you'll free the kingdom from the heavy yoke of their terror. Fail, and the malicious gods rule on, as the Acolytes rise anew, and madness prevails.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ray's The Dead.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Ray's The Dead.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ray's The Dead.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20200821T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ragtag Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Ragtag Studio</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Skul - The Hero Slayer.lnk</path>
		<name>Skul - The Hero Slayer</name>
		<desc>The Demon King's Castle in Ruins The human race attacking the Demon King's castle is nothing new and has happened countless times before. What makes this time different though, is that the Adventurers decided to join forces with the Imperial Army and the 'Hero of Caerleon' to lead a full onslaught in hopes of wiping out the Demons once and for all. They attacked the Demon stronghold with overwhelming numbers and succeeded in its total destruction. All of the demons in the castle were taken prisoner except for one lone skeleton named 'Skul'. Side-Scrolling Platformer Action 'Skul: The Hero Slayer' is an action-platformer that boasts rogue-like features such as everchanging and challenging maps. It will keep you on your toes, as you will never know what to expect. Tons of skulls, tons of playable characters Skul is no ordinary skeleton. In addition to his formidable fighting skills, he can gain new and exciting abilities depending on which skull he's wearing. Use up to 2 skulls at a time, each of which has its own unique attack range, speed and power.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Skul - The Hero Slayer.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Skul - The Hero Slayer.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Skul - The Hero Slayer.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20200821T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Southpaw Games</developer>
		<publisher>NEOWIZ</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Streets of Rage 4.lnk</path>
		<name>Streets of Rage 4</name>
		<desc>The all-time classic Streets of Rage, known as Bare Knuckle (ベア・ナックル Bea Nakkuru) in Japan, is a trilogy of beat ‘em up known for this timeless gameplay and electronic dance influenced music. Streets of Rage 4 builds upon the classic trilogy’s gameplay with new mechanics, beautiful hand drawn visuals and a God tier soundtrack. Or team up along to defeat the Boss Rush Mode!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Streets of Rage 4.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Streets of Rage 4.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Streets of Rage 4.png</marquee>
		<rating>4.41</rating>
		<releasedate>20200430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DotEmu, Guard Crush Games, Lizardcube</developer>
		<publisher>DotEmu</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Beat 'em Up</genre>
		<players>3</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Streets of Rogue.lnk</path>
		<name>Streets of Rogue</name>
		<desc>Streets of Rogue is a rogue-lite about player choice, freedom, and anarchic fun. The game takes inspiration from fast-paced top-down rogue-lites like Binding of Isaac and Nuclear Throne, and adds free-form, experimentation-driven, emergent gameplay elements of RPGs like Deus Ex. In order to progress, the player will need to accomplish specific mission goals in any way they see fit through use of their special character traits, items, and the environment.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Streets of Rogue.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Streets of Rogue.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Streets of Rogue.png</marquee>
		<rating>4.36</rating>
		<releasedate>20170310T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Matt Dabrowski</developer>
		<publisher>tinyBuild</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./System Shock - Enhanced Edition.lnk</path>
		<name>System Shock - Enhanced Edition</name>
		<desc>A first-person fight to the death in the depths of space. You're a renowned hacker, the most notorious cyberspace thief in the corporate world. Caught during a risky break-in, you become indentured to Diego, a greedy Trioptium exec who bankrolls a rare cyberjack implant operation. After six months in a healing coma, you awaken to the twisted aftermath of a terrible disaster. Where are the surgeons? Why is the station in such disrepair? Slowly, the chilling realization that something is very wrong creeps over you. Once a prime corporate research facility, Citadel now teems with mindless cyborgs, robots and terribly mutated beings, all programmed to serve SHODAN, a ruthless A.I. There's scarcely time to think before it unleashes the first terror... Twenty one years after its first release, System Shock is back! The Enhanced Edition adds a modern touch to this true classic gem, without taking anything from its unmistakable atmosphere. See for yourself that the game that has been called the benchmark for intelligent first-person gaming, has lost nothing of its ability to keep you on the edge of your seat. System Shock: Enhanced Edition features: Higher resolution support: up to 1024x768, and 854x480 widescreen mode. Mouselook support added. Remappable keys with three profiles to choose from: original controls, custom controls, and lefthanded controls. Some original game bugs fixed. Gameplay features: Rocket through cyberspace to steal information, hack security and grapple with watchdog defense programs enslaved to a maniacal computer. Survive battle after battle against armies of killer cyborgs and deadly robots as you collect hardware attachments, life-sustaining patches and deadly weapons to combat mindless mutants. Test your intelligence by solving puzzles, rewiring access panels and outwitting SHODAN in its own cyber-realm. Enjoy the vastly improved controls and graphics of the Enhanced Edition - or keep your experience as close to the original as possible with the Classic version.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/System Shock - Enhanced Edition.png</image>
		<video>./snap/System Shock - Enhanced Edition.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/System Shock - Enhanced Edition.png</marquee>
		<rating>3.92</rating>
		<releasedate>20150922T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Looking Glass Studios, Nightdive Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Nightdive Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./TMNT HD.lnk</path>
		<name>TMNT HD</name>
		<desc>Classic TMNT from nes to HD 2d style: TMNT takes the fearsome foursome through a series of acrobatic battles amidst the dark and gritty streets, sewers, subways, and rooftops of New York City.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/TMNT HD 4.9.png</image>
		<video>./snap/TMNT HD 4.9.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/TMNT HD 4.9.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20201201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Fanmade</developer>
		<publisher>fanmade</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Toki.lnk</path>
		<name>Toki</name>
		<desc>The hero of the game is a young jungle-man named Toki. One day the evil wizard Dr. Stark kidnaps his girlfriend Wanda. When Toki tries to save her, he is turned into a monkey! Now Toki has to find Dr. Stark in his palace, to rescue Wanda, and to become a human being again!

It is a platform game with a lot of various levels: jungle, underwater, volcanic caves, on the ice... Toki's only weapons are spitting on the enemies or jumping on them and crashing them. There are many possibilities to upgrade his spitting "weapon";  for example, if he finds an upgrade, he can spit fireballs. 

This game is ported from an older arcade version.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Toki.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Toki.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Toki.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19911201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tad Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>dc7ff8f3b7fcee21cb7fff9a2cf72cbf</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tomb Raider Anniversary.lnk</path>
		<name>Tomb Raider: Anniversary</name>
		<desc>A remake of the first video game in the series, the original Tomb Raider. It uses an improved version of the Legend game engine, and it includes all of the original environments from Tomb Raider.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Tomb Raider.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Tomb.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tomb Raider Anniversary.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20070601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crystal Dynamics, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Puzzle, Strategy, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>dcea931cbeb118f5584d9fa5a33b2258</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="12255">
		<path>./Trine 2.lnk</path>
		<name>Trine 2 Complete Story</name>
		<desc>Trine Enchanted Edition is a remastered version for WiiU of Trine's first opus. Players can now relive the adventure with improved graphics and the arrival of a multiplayer mode.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Trine 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Trine 2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Trine 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nobilis</developer>
		<publisher>Frozenbyte</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>3</players>
		<md5>2a9235e4ebae80f322398658540e4ca1</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Turok 2 Seeds of Evil Remastered.lnk</path>
		<name>Turok 2 Seeds of Evil Remastered</name>
		<desc>The Dinosaur Hunter Returns! Fight your way through 35 different types of enemies with bouncing bellies, blinking eyes, stretching tentacles and snapping jaws. From Prehistoric Raptors, to evolved Flesh Eaters, to your final battle with the Mother of all beasts— you’ll want to defeat all of them!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Turok 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Turok 2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Turok 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19981210T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Iguana Entertainment, Nightdive Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Nightdive Studios</publisher>
		<genre>First Person Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>7c91204ff0a8d82d1d02a0246a3e2f08</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Turok Dinosaur Hunter Remaster.lnk</path>
		<name>Turok Dinosaur Hunter Remaster</name>
		<desc>Turok is back and no dinosaur is safe! When it was first released in 1997, Turok introduced gamers to a world teeming with cunning enemies, traps, puzzles and deadly weapons all within a vast 3D environment ready to explore. Now the classic game has been restored and enhanced with a new visual engine and exciting new features to sink your teeth into!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Turok.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Turok.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Turok.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19971130T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Iguana Entertainment, Nightdive Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Nightdive Studios</publisher>
		<genre>First Person Shooter</genre>
		<md5>5342c3a7da468e7b3385794359b3b119</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./UnderMine.lnk</path>
		<name>UnderMine</name>
		<desc>An action-adventure roguelike with a bit of RPG tossed in. Adventure deep into the UnderMine and discover powerful relics, deadly enemies, hidden secrets, and a few friends to help along the way. UnderMine has a rich world to explore and discover with charming characters and a plot full of intrigue. Experience the plight of the poor Delvemore peasants. Told to brave extreme danger for a boss that doesn't quite care about them or their safety. A pretty funny situation when you think about it and something we can all relate to.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/UnderMine.png</image>
		<video>./snap/UnderMine.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/UnderMine.png</marquee>
		<rating>3.08</rating>
		<releasedate>20190101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Thorium</developer>
		<publisher>Fandom, Thorium</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Unravel Two.lnk</path>
		<name>Unravel Two</name>
		<desc>Unravel Two is a puzzle-platform game developed by Swedish studio Coldwood Interactive and published by Electronic Arts. It is the sequel to Unravel from 2016.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Unravel Two.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Unravel Two.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Unravel Two.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20180609T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ColdWood Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Puzzle, Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>a9fc441dcbb482c768539a467420908a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="228213">
		<path>./Unruly Heroes.lnk</path>
		<name>Unruly Heroes</name>
		<desc>The sacred scroll preserving harmony in our world has been torn up and scattered to the winds. Now, strange and terrifying creatures are sowing discord and chaos throughout the land. Inspired by the timeless Chinese novel "Journey to the West," Unruly Heroes tells the adventure of four totally opposed, implausible heroes who must collect all the scroll fragments and travel to fantastical worlds to restore balance... or die trying!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Unruly Heroes.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Unruly.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Unruly Heroes.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>201901231T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Magic Design Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Magic Design Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<md5>53bbdf7b94f0dc0cfa7d2e721d611b81</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./VASARA Collection.lnk</path>
		<name>VASARA Collection</name>
		<desc>For the very first time, highly acclaimed Japanese Arcade Shoot’em Ups - VASARA (2000) and VASARA 2 (2001) - are made available to the whole world via this package: VASARA COLLECTION!

Science Fiction meets History in these arcade classics which take place in an alternate timeline Feudal Japan where technologically advanced weaponry and equipment are a reality, and heroes use flying motorcycles with amazing firepower and fierce melee weapons to destroy their enemies.
Try and stay alive on this frantic game where everyone, and everything, is out to kill you!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Vasara Collection.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Vasara.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Vasara Collection.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20190813T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>QUByte Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>QUByte Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<md5>e7ff5372baf4dcd03eeb8b8fd743cc6b</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./VirtuaVerse.lnk</path>
		<name>VirtuaVerse</name>
		<desc>Set in a future not-so-far-away, VirtuaVerse is a cyberpunk point-and-click adventure weaving tales of Technomancers, AVR graffiti writers, hacker gangs, tribes of cryptoshamans, epic cyberwars, digital archaeology, and virtual reality debauchery. Jack in. Spread the code. Look at VirtuaVerse.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/VirtuaVerse.png</image>
		<video>./snap/VirtuaVerse.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/VirtuaVerse.png</marquee>
		<rating>3.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20200512T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Theta Division</developer>
		<publisher>Blood Music</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wacky Wheels HD Remake.lnk</path>
		<name>Wacky Wheels HD Remake</name>
		<desc>Play as eight wacky animals in Wacky Wheels. Each animal has its own colorful antics and animations, including a tiger, elephant, raccoon, panda, shark, and more. These animals are incredibly competitive - they hate to lose! They take great joy in bumping, scraping and knocking you off the track. They want you at the back of the pack!

Nothing beats the competitive feel of racing. Feel the thrill as you race past your opponent, slam their car into a water trap, and beat them by a bumper to the finish line. Avoid obstacles, knock opponents, launch weapons, take shortcuts, engage turbo mode, and hit jumps with perfect timing to outrace your opponent every time!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Wacky Wheels HD.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Wacky.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Wacky Wheels HD.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>199410171T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Beavis Soft</developer>
		<publisher>3D Realms</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<md5>5f46cf04d82982f5f7d5fb9919df6399</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Warcraft - Orcs and Humans.lnk</path>
		<name>Warcraft - Orcs and Humans</name>
		<desc>The Kingdom of Azeroth was relatively peaceful and ruled by King Llane. That was until a powerful mage named Medivh commanded forces that opened up a portal in the Swamp of Sorrow, leading to another world. This ushered in the Age of Chaos, as Orcs were summoned to this world and attempted to establish an empire. As the Orcish hordes swarmed from the portal, they met with the Humans of Azeroth and battles ensured. Peaceful co-existence is not an option. Only one race will attain dominance over the land. Warcraft: Orcs and Humans is the first real-time fantasy strategy game from Blizzard Entertainment. By playing either the Humans or the Orcs in this saga, two separate story lines evolve with 12 scenarios per side telling the tale of the battle for Azeroth. Players must mine gold and chop wood in order to construct buildings and create new units. From swords to sorcery, all the elements of classic fantasy are here to explore: rich forests, dark dungeons and bubbling swamps await the stalwart troops amassed to fight for dominance. Command many unique armies and creatures including Knights, Archers, Clerics, Warlocks, Daemons, Elementals, and Necromancers who are able to raise the dead. The multiplayer aspects of the game allow 2 players to challenge one another on over 20 custom maps and determine who is the supreme warlord. Head to head play is supported over modem, serial link, and IPX networks, and works cross-platform between the IBM-PC and Macintosh versions.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Warcraft - Orcs and Humans.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Warcraft - Orcs and Humans.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Warcraft - Orcs and Humans.png</marquee>
		<rating>4.12</rating>
		<releasedate>19940115T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Blizzard Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./World of Final Fantasy.lnk</path>
		<name>World of Final Fantasy: Maxima</name>
		<desc>Originally released in October 2016, WORLD OF FINAL FANTASY is now available on PC as the powered-up FINAL FANTASY Maxima! Beloved characters from FF lore (Champions) and a multitude of capturable monsters (Mirages) appear in this fun and exciting adventure. This new and enhanced version of WORLD OF FINAL FANTASY also features the Avatar Change system, which allows the protagonists, Reynn and Lann, to fight as Champions. Fight your way through exhilarating battles as legendary FINAL FANTASY heroes!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/World of Final Fantasy.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/World of Final Fantasy.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/World of Final Fantasy.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20180821T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./The Take Over.lnk</path>
		<name>The Take Over</name>
		<desc>The Takeover is a side-scrolling beat'em up inspired by 90's classics such as Streets of Rage and Final Fight. Battle solo or alongside a friend in local co-op in any of the three featured game modes, Arcade, Survival and Challenge. Fight your way across 7 stages and over 20 unique locations using any of the four playable characters or swap between them in real time in the unlockable Relay Mode.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/The Take Over.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/The TakeOver.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/The Take Over.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20191110T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pelikan13</developer>
		<publisher>Pelikan13</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<md5>330685398d2169e750d80779ca44135a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cobra Kai The Karate Kid Saga Continues.lnk</path>
		<name>Cobra Kai The Karate Kid Saga Continues</name>
		<desc>Choose a side, master your moves, and embrace your destiny in an epic beat 'em up adventure inspired by the hit show. Take control of 8 playable characters with deep movesets, combos, progression, real-time character swaps, ultimate attacks, and much more! 34 years after the events of the 1984 All Valley Karate Tournament, the rivalry of Daniel LaRusso and Johnny Lawrence continues. The fight is in your hands now! •Two-Fold Storyline - Featuring an all-new storyline filled with unique cutscenes and dialog-choose to take control of Daniel and his students at Miyagi-Do Karate through a storyline campaign.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Cobra Kai The Karate Kid Saga Continues.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Cobra Kai The Karate Kid Saga Continues.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Cobra Kai The Karate Kid Saga Continues.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20201201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Flux Game Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Gamemill Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Curse of the Dead Gods.lnk</path>
		<name>Curse of the Dead Gods</name>
		<desc>You seek untold riches, eternal life, divine powers - it leads to this accursed temple, a seemingly-infinite labyrinth of bottomless pits, deadly traps, and monsters. Your greed will lead you to death, but that is not an escape. Rise to fight again. Delve deeper again. Defy the malignant deities that linger in this place. Battle through hordes of enemies in dark, cavernous passages filled with traps and secrets of all sorts - fire-spewing statues, explosives, hidden spikes, and worse. Collect mystical Relics and an arsenal of weapons to make yourself unstoppable. Corruption builds in you with every step - encourage or ignore it, but each powerful curse can be a double-edged sword. - A skill-based roguelike exploring a cruel, dark temple made of endless rooms and corridors - Swords, spears, bows, guns - wield these and many more - Unique curses influence each attempt, putting a twist on every action - Dozens of enemies, with powerful champions and deadly bosses to face off against.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Curse of the Dead Gods.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Curse of the Dead Gods.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Curse of the Dead Gods.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20210821T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Passtech Games</developer>
		<publisher>Focus Home Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kaze and the Wild Masks.lnk</path>
		<name>Kaze and the Wild Masks</name>
		<desc>Journey through the Crystal Islands in 90’s classics platformer style. Play as Kaze and save your friend Hogo from a curse that spread chaos around the islands. Face enraged living vegetables by invoking the powers of the wild masks. Pounce ferociously like a tiger, soar through the sky like an eagle, sprint fiercely like a lizard and rule the sea like a shark. Features • Unleash the skills of the Wild Masks to get powers from the tiger, eagle, lizard and shark • Uncover the secrets of the Crystal Islands through collectables, achievements and 50+ bonus levels • Relive your childhood memories of classic platformers with high quality frame by frame pixel art • Pave your way through a satisfyingly smooth, but challenging platformer.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Kaze and the Wild Masks.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Kaze and the Wild Masks.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Kaze and the Wild Masks.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>20200430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vox Game Studio</developer>
		<publisher>SOEDESCO</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./New Super Lucky's Tale.lnk</path>
		<name>New Super Lucky's Tale</name>
		<desc>Join Lucky on his thrilling journey through the Book of Ages, a magical artifact that opens doors to amazing worlds. Meet new friends, explore exciting lands, and recover the missing pages from the evil sorcerer Jinx and his villainous family, the dreaded Kitty Litter. • Featuring a huge variety of gameplay, from expansive 3D hubs, to story-based adventure levels, 2D side-scrolling challenges, rewarding mini-games, mind-bending puzzles, and thrilling boss battles.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/New Super Lucky's Tale.png</image>
		<video>./snap/New Super Lucky's Tale.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/New Super Lucky's Tale.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20200430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Playful Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Playful Corp.</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./The Messenger.lnk</path>
		<name>The Messenger</name>
		<desc>As a demon army besieges his village, a young ninja ventures through a cursed world, to deliver a scroll paramount to his clan’s survival. What begins as a classic action platformer soon unravels into an expansive time-traveling adventure full of thrills, surprises, and humor. - Dynamic, acrobatic gameplay and ultra tight controls worthy of an epic ninja adventure. - Character upgrades, new abilities, hidden levels, and branching paths to discover. - Meticulously designed 8-bit and 16-bit sprites, animations, and backgrounds in the spirit of the classics. - A memorable cast of offbeat villains, bosses, and associates.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/The Messenger.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/The Messenger.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/The Messenger.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>20180430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sabotage Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Devolver Digital</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fury Unleashed.lnk</path>
		<name>Fury Unleashed</name>
		<desc>Fury Unleashed is an action platformer where you shoot your way through the pages of an ever-changing comic book. Take advantage of unique combo system to unleash your fury and become a whirling tornado of destruction. Discover why your creator doubted in you and prove him wrong. MAIN FEATURES: - Comic book setting – Play through the pages of a living comic book with Metal Slug inspired visuals. - Intriguing storyline - Find out why is John Kowalsky, author of acclaimed Fury Unleashed, series having a creativity crisis and see if you can help him deal with it. - Local co-op mode - Bring in your sidekick to increase your chances and double the fun. - Action platforming with 360° shooting – jump, dash, shoot and slash in any direction. Movement options are limitless, it's up to you to choose the best angle to deal with a given set of enemies. - Gameplay-impacting combo system - if you can kill enemies quickly enough, your power will increase and you will be able to take some hits without getting damaged. It's even possible to beat the entire game in one combo!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Fury Unleashed.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Fury Unleashed.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Fury Unleashed.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>20170430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Awesome Games Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Awesome Games Studio</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./The Wonderful 101 Remastered.lnk</path>
		<name>The Wonderful 101 Remastered</name>
		<desc>Fury Unleashed is an action platformer where you shoot your way through the pages of an ever-changing comic book. Take advantage of unique combo system to unleash your fury and become a whirling tornado of destruction. Discover why your creator doubted in you and prove him wrong. MAIN FEATURES: - Comic book setting – Play through the pages of a living comic book with Metal Slug inspired visuals. - Intriguing storyline - Find out why is John Kowalsky, author of acclaimed Fury Unleashed, series having a creativity crisis and see if you can help him deal with it. - Local co-op mode - Bring in your sidekick to increase your chances and double the fun. - Action platforming with 360° shooting – jump, dash, shoot and slash in any direction. Movement options are limitless, it's up to you to choose the best angle to deal with a given set of enemies. - Gameplay-impacting combo system - if you can kill enemies quickly enough, your power will increase and you will be able to take some hits without getting damaged. It's even possible to beat the entire game in one combo!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/The Wonderful 101 Remastered.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/The Wonderful 101 Remastered.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/The Wonderful 101 Remastered.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20200430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>PlatinumGames</developer>
		<publisher>PlatinumGames</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cyber Shadow.lnk</path>
		<name>Cyber Shadow</name>
		<desc>The world has been taken over by synthetic lifeforms. A desperate plea for help sets Shadow on a journey to uncover what started the path to perpetual ruin. Slash through the techno hordes, leap past traps, and nimbly navigate the ruins of Mekacity. Only you can unlock the secrets to your clan’s ancient powers in Cyber Shadow, the quintessential Ninja Action game.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Cyber Shadow.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Cyber Shadow.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Cyber Shadow.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20211201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mechanical Head-Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Yacht Club-Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Moonlighter.lnk</path>
		<name>Moonlighter</name>
		<desc>Moonlighter is an Action RPG with rogue-lite elements following the everyday routines of Will, an adventurous shopkeeper that dreams of becoming a hero. Confront unfamiliar mini-bosses using brand-new weapons, armor, rings and amulets. Wander around 100 fresh room patterns, with the help of 9 brave Companions, and discover even more lore and story. Finish the main adventure to unlock New Game+ mode with additional challenges and options.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Moonlighter.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Moonlighter.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Moonlighter.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20180529T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Sun</developer>
		<publisher>11 bit studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Narita Boy.lnk</path>
		<name>Narita Boy</name>
		<desc>The retro-futuristic pixel game. Explore and fight in a retro-futuristic world. Swim deep into a oneiric, poetic and unique experience across dimensional planes. The aesthetic of the game was inspired by retro pixel adventures (Castlevania, Another World, Double Dragon) with a modern touch. And an 80s plot homage (Ready Player One, He-Man, The Last Starfighter), accompanied by the retro synth touch of the old glory days.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Narita Boy.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Narita Boy.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Narita Boy.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20210821T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Studio Koba</developer>
		<publisher>Team17</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Oceans Heart.lnk</path>
		<name>Ocean's Heart</name>
		<desc>Ocean’s Heart is an action RPG featuring detailed pixel art with a heavy focus on exploration. In a lively world teeming with secrets and mysteries, Tilia sets out in search of her missing father. Follow the trail through the ruins of a flooded kingdom, shape the future of the current world, or keep your head down and focus on your own mission in this epic retro-inspired adventure!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Oceans Heart.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Oceans Heart.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Oceans Heart.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20210121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Max Mraz</developer>
		<publisher>Nordcurrent</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Stubbs The Zombie.lnk</path>
		<name>Stubbs The Zombie</name>
		<desc>Stubbs the Zombie in Rebel Without a Pulse is a 3D action game that turns the tables on the age old tradition of zombie games. In this game, you play as the zombie, fight off the humans, and eat their brains. Stubbs the Zombie is set in a retro-futuristic city of the future and follows Stubbs over the course of one day as he zombifies the entire city. Before becoming a zombie Edward 'Stubbs' Stubblefield was a traveling salesman in the 1930s who got himself killed. Flash forward to 1959 where the world's richest man, Andrew Monday, has built his dream city, Punchbowl Pennsylvania, on top of poor Stubbs' grave. Stubbs will have to claw through all of Punchbowl's citizens, including the local police department, crazy militiamen, nerdy scientists, and a deadly barbershop quartet. Luckily Stubbs has some help.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Stubbs The Zombie.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Stubbs The Zombie.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Stubbs The Zombie.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20060821T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wideload Games</developer>
		<publisher>Aspyr Media</publisher>
		<genre>Arcade, Horror</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sword of the Necromancer.lnk</path>
		<name>Sword of the Necromancer</name>
		<desc>Sword of the Necromancer is a dungeon-crawler action RPG with Rogue-like elements where you can revive your defeated enemies to make them fight alongside you.

Turn your foes into allies using the forbidden powers of the Sword of the Necromancer and help Tama reach the dungeon’s depths in order to gain enough power to bring Koko back from the dead.

Gather a little army of monsters, equip yourself with weapons and relics and level up to take on the guardians that stand between you and your objective.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Sword of the Necromancer.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Sword of the Necromancer.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sword of the Necromancer.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20210821T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Grimorio of Games</developer>
		<publisher>JanduSoft</publisher>
		<genre>Arcade, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Town of Machine.lnk</path>
		<name>Town of Machine</name>
		<desc>700 years from now, Agent Silverman is a renowned Exorcist on the case of a missing person. His investigation leads him to a small ghost town called "Town of Machine". Uncover unspeakable horrors and fight the grotesque monstrosities that lurk in this forsaken place.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Town of Machine.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Town of Machine.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Town of Machine.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20210821T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>BlueEagle Productions</developer>
		<publisher>BlueEagle Productions</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Worms W.M.D.lnk</path>
		<name>Worms W.M.D</name>
		<desc>The worms are back in their most destructive game yet. With a gorgeous, hand-drawn 2D look, brand new weapons, the introduction of crafting, vehicles and buildings plus the return of some much-loved classic weapons and gameplay, Worms W.M.D is the best worms experience ever.

Work your way through 30 campaign levels of increasing difficulty using the huge arsenal of new and classic weapons at your disposal. Use new vehicles to cause chaos amongst the enemy ranks and use buildings to gain the tactical advantage as you try to dominate the battlefield!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Worms wmd.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Worms.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Worms wmd.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20160823T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team17</developer>
		<publisher>Team17</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Journey.lnk</path>
		<name>Journey</name>
		<desc>Explore the ancient, mysterious world of Journey as you soar above ruins and glide across sands to discover its secrets. Play alone or in the company of a fellow traveler and explore its vast world together. Featuring stunning visuals and a Grammy-nominated musical score, Journey delivers a breathtaking experience like no other.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Journey.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Journey.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Journey.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20190430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ThatGameCompany</developer>
		<publisher>Annapurna Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fable Anniversary.lnk</path>
		<name>Fable Anniversary</name>
		<desc>FOR EVERY CHOICE, A CONSEQUENCE. Fully re-mastered with HD visuals and audio, Fable Anniversary is a stunning rendition of the original game that will delight faithful fans and new players alike! The all new Heroic difficulty setting will test the mettle of even the most hardcore Fable fan.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Fable Anniversary.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Fable Anniversary.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Fable Anniversary.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20141201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Lionhead Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./RAD.lnk</path>
		<name>RAD</name>
		<desc>RAD is a 3D action rogue-like set in a post-post-apocalyptic world, where humanity has faced armageddon not once, but twice. Playing as a teenage protagonist, you must venture into the Fallow — an ever-changing, radioactive wasteland filled with unknown and unspeakable creatures. But humanity’s future comes at great personal cost, as the deeper you journey into unknown lands, the more you will expose yourself to gnarly toxins which will wreak havoc on your fragile human form. The fate of the world depends on you, your trusty bat, and whatever strange new abilities you gain as the world around you ravages your body — twisting and mutating you into something far less than human, but far more powerful. But forget all that — go grab that sweet bat and help save the world…or what’s remaining of it anyway!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/RAD.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/RAD.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/RAD.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20191201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Double Fine Productions</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai NAMCO</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Transistor.lnk</path>
		<name>Transistor</name>
		<desc>Transistor is a sci-fi themed action RPG from the creators of Bastion that invites players to wield an extraordinary weapon of unknown origin as they fight through a stunning futuristic city. The game seamlessly integrates thoughtful strategic planning into a fast-paced action experience, melding responsive gameplay and rich atmospheric storytelling. During the course of the adventure, players will piece together the Transistor's mysteries as they pursue its former owners. Red, a famous singer in a city called Cloudbank, is attacked by the Process, a robotic force commanded by a group called the Camerata. During the clash, she is transported all the way across Cloudbank and comes into possession of the mysterious Transistor- the greatsword-like weapon she was to be assassinated with. The Transistor is buried into the chest of an unnamed man, now slumped over and dead; though his consciousness and voice seems to have been absorbed into the Transistor itself, along with Red's voice. The Camerata continues to track Red and the Transistor down with the Process, wanting the weapon for some yet-unknown cause.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Transistor.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Transistor.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Transistor.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>20141201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Supergiant Games</developer>
		<publisher>Supergiant Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Halo - Spartan Assault.lnk</path>
		<name>Halo - Spartan Assault</name>
		<desc>"Halo: Spartan Assault" is a new top-down action shooter that brings a "Halo" video game to touch-based devices for the first time in franchise history. Developed by 343 Industries in conjunction with Vanguard Games, "Halo: Spartan Assault" provides an accessible, pick-up-and-play experience for fans and newcomers alike. Set between the events of "Halo 3" and "Halo 4," "Halo: Spartan Assault" is a new chapter of the award-winning "Halo" universe that explores the first missions of the Spartan Ops program and dives deeper into the backstory of Human-Covenant wars. Play through the eyes of either Commander Sarah Palmer or Spartan Davis stationed aboard the UNSC Infinity as they fight never-before-seen battles against Covenant forces. With rich storytelling, intuitive controls, and best-in-class action, audio and graphics, "Halo: Spartan Assault" brings the epic scale and action of the "Halo" universe to mobile devices through unrivaled action and intensity.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Halo - Spartan Assault.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Halo - Spartan Assault.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Halo - Spartan Assault.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20131201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>343 Industries</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./INSIDE.lnk</path>
		<name>INSIDE</name>
		<desc>Inside (stylized as INSIDE) is a puzzle-platformer adventure video game developed and published by independent studio Playdead. In the game the player controls a young boy in a monochromatic landscape, solving environmental puzzles while avoiding death in a 3D sidescrolling fashion, thematically and visually similar to Playdead's earlier game Limbo. The game starts with a nameless, red-shirted boy sliding down a rocky incline in a forest. While running through the forest, he encounters forest guards wearing masks, who are either inspecting the forest or are intent on chasing and/or killing the boy. A truck can be seen driving off into the near industrial facility.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/INSIDE.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/INSIDE.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/INSIDE.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20161201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Playdead</developer>
		<publisher>Playdead</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zombie Driver HD.lnk</path>
		<name>Zombie Driver HD</name>
		<desc>Insane mix of cars, speed, explosions, blood and zombies! Fight through an epic narrative campaign or test yourself in the Slaughter and Blood Race modes. Engage huge bosses, save survivors, drive crazy vehicles such as a bulldozer, fire truck or even a tank and smash everything in your way. Take part in the Blood Race tournament - chase other cars and take them down without mercy on brutal racing tracks. Jump into the Slaughter mode and survive as long as possible on specially crafted arenas.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Zombie Driver HD.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Zombie Driver HD.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Zombie Driver HD.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20121201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Exor Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Exor Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rise Of The Argonauts.lnk</path>
		<name>Rise Of The Argonauts</name>
		<desc>As the King of Iolcus, Jason had everything—a prosperous kingdom, the respect of his peers, and a beautiful fiancé. When she was killed on their wedding day, he vowed to do anything to restore her life.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Rise Of The Argonauts.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Rise Of The Argonauts.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Rise Of The Argonauts.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20081201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Liquid Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Deadcells.lnk</path>
		<name>Dead Cells</name>
		<desc>Dead Cells is a rogue-lite, metroidvania inspired, action-platformer. You'll explore a sprawling, ever-changing castle... assuming you’re able to fight your way past its keepers in 2D souls-lite combat. No checkpoints. Kill, die, learn, repeat. Roguelite? Metroidvania? Roguevania! You grew up with the roguelikes, witnessed the rise of the roguelites and even the birth of the roguelite-lites? We'd now like to present for your consideration our RogueVania, the illegitimate child of a modern Roguelite (Rogue Legacy, Binding of Isaac, Enter the Gungeon, Spelunky, etc.) and an old-school MetroidVania (Castlevania: SotN and its ilk).</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Deadcells.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Deadcells.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Deadcells.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>20181201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Motion Twin</developer>
		<publisher>Motion Twin</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform-RPG</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Death's Gambit.lnk</path>
		<name>Death's Gambit</name>
		<desc>Death's Gambit is a challenging 2D action platformer with deep RPG elements. As an agent of Death bound to his service, unravel the mystery of Siradon and discover the true price of immortality. The promise of immortality lies at the heart of Siradon. As Death's right hand, challenge the undying guardians of the realm and endure the eternal struggle to purge their souls. But what reward awaits a faithful servant of Death? Death's Gambit is a hardcore 2D action platformer with rich RPG elements. Master the precise combat, utilizing a wide variety of weapons and abilities to confront the horrors that lurk deep within Siradon. Explore a mysterious and unforgiving world to uncover the true price of immortality. Embrace the challenge of being an agent of Death. Expansive World - Travel across the beautifully rendered Obsidian Vale, Witch Woods, Sanguine City, and more. Meet quirky characters from all walks of life, and uncover their narrative threads and secrets.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Death's Gambit.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Death's Gambit.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Death's Gambit.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>20181201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>White Rabbit</developer>
		<publisher>Adult Swim Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Pixel Racers.lnk</path>
		<name>Super Pixel Racers</name>
		<desc>Super Pixel Racers is a fast-paced arcade racer with top-down 2D pixel graphics and a nostalgic 16-bit soundtrack. The game lets you hop straight into the driver’s seat, but advanced features let players customize their racing experience even further. Your winnings let you purchase new cars of individual driving quality and upgrade schemes, from a pixelated F500 to your very own 16-bit Lancer Evolution. As the game progresses, find out which car suits the different disciplines and yourself best. Some features to look forward to are: Rally Cross: Classic race against up to 7 other drivers Rally: Reach checkpoints on a procedurally generated outdoor track Land Rush: Be in front of the pack when the time ends Takedown: Destroy the other cars Hunt: Chase the target down Drift Show: Score points by drifting Thirteen Unique Racetracks: From desert dunes to the city streets. A host of unique pixel environments set the stage for some truly super pixel racing.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Super Pixel Racers.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Super Pixel Racers.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Super Pixel Racers.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20201201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>21c.Ducks</developer>
		<publisher>H2 Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./10 Second Ninja X.lnk</path>
		<name>10 Second Ninja X</name>
		<desc>Ninjas are cool, this is an established fact of the universe. Nazi Robots from space are not cool, they are the complete opposite of cool, and Robot Hitler is out to get you, the world's first ninja. You have 10 seconds to destroy all Nazi Robots in your vicinity. IT. IS. ON. Become the ultimate Ninja and take down Robot Hitler’s automated autocracy in this blisteringly fast platformer. Ready, Steady, Ninja!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/10 Second Ninja X.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/10 Second Ninja X.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/10 Second Ninja X.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>20141201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>GameDesignDan</developer>
		<publisher>Mastertronic</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Brutal Legend.lnk</path>
		<name>Brutal Legend</name>
		<desc>From the mind of Tim Schafer (Psychonauts, Grim Fandango) comes Brütal Legend, the ultimate heavy metal action game starring Jack Black (School of Rock, Tenacious D). You are heavy metal roadie Eddie Riggs, hurled back in time to the mythical Age of Metal when the world was formed and ruled by the power of Rock! Armed with a broadaxe, a guitar, and a big block V8 you set off on an epic quest to assemble an army of headbangers, hot rods, barbarians, demonic dominatrix, and the undead. With the wings of a demon and the power of a Rock God, you must lead humanity in an epic war against its barbaric overlords, and carve your name forever into the Brutal Legend.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Brutal Legend.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Brutal Legend.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Brutal Legend.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>20131201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Double Fine Productions</developer>
		<publisher>Double Fine Productions</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dust - An Elysian Tail.lnk</path>
		<name>Dust - An Elysian Tail</name>
		<desc>Immerse yourself in a gorgeous hand-painted world on a search for your true identity. As the mysterious warrior, Dust, your action-packed journey will take you from peaceful glades to snowy mountaintops and beyond. At your disposal is the mythical Blade of Ahrah, capable of turning its wielder into an unstoppable force of nature, and the blade's diminutive guardian, Fidget. Battle dozens of enemies at once with an easy-to-learn, difficult-to-master combat system, take on a variety of quests from friendly villagers, discover ancient secrets and powerful upgrades hidden throughout the massive, open world, and uncover the story of an ancient civilization on the brink of extinction as you fight to uncover your own past.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Dust - An Elysian Tail.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Dust - An Elysian Tail.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dust - An Elysian Tail.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>20131201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Humble Hearts</developer>
		<publisher>Humble Hearts</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bionic Commando Rearmed.lnk</path>
		<name>Bionic Commando Rearmed</name>
		<desc>Classic side-scrolling gameplay is reporting back for duty with Bionic Commando Rearmed, a remake of the classic NES game, out now on PC. 20 years after the 8-bit classic was released, Bionic Commando Rearmed recreates the world of the original with a complete "2.5D" visual revamp. Bionic Commando Rearmed preserves the original's mix of swinging and shooting in an intense 2D side-scroller, all to the tune of a brand-new soundtrack based on the classic 8-bit music from the NES masterpiece. But Rearmed is far more than just a remake - it features all-new modes such as the 2-player co-op play, smarter enemy AI, new bionic arm abilities, new weapons, bigger bosses and online rankings.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Bionic Commando Rearmed.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Bionic Commando Rearmed.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Bionic Commando Rearmed.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20081201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>GRIN AB</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SteamWorld - Heist.lnk</path>
		<name>SteamWorld - Heist</name>
		<desc>From the makers of SteamWorld Dig: In SteamWorld Heist, you command a steam-driven pirate crew in a series of epic tactical shootouts. It’s turn-based strategy with a twist: You manually aim the guns of your robots, allowing for insane skill shots and bullet-bouncing action! As the captain you will board, loot and shoot your way through enemy spaceships. Overcome the challenges of the vast frontier by upgrading your recruits with unique abilities, weapons – and even stylish hats! KEY FEATURES - Strategy focused on skill rather than chance - Procedurally generated levels - 15-20 hours of playtime, followed by New Game+ - Kind to newcomers, deep and challenging for veterans.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/SteamWorld - Heist.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/SteamWorld - Heist.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/SteamWorld - Heist.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>201601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Image Form</developer>
		<publisher>Image Form</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bastion.lnk</path>
		<name>Bastion</name>
		<desc>Bastion is an isometric action/role playing game. It's the story of a city known as Caelondia after it has been destroyed by a disaster called "Calamity". The game follows a silent protagonist known as "The Kid" who tries to create a safe haven (Bastion) with the help of Rucks, who is also the narrator of the game. The kid has to defeat the game's many foes with a variety of melee and ranged weapons and also special skills. The Bastion, which acts as some sort of headquarters in the game, can be upgraded with useful buildings as the player progresses. As the Kid travels through the world, he will discover new weapons, upgrade materials, mementos and fragments. Mementos can be discussed with other characters residing in the Bastion and may reveal more about the world.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Bastion.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Bastion.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Bastion.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>201101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Supergiant Games</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Bros.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sundered Eldritch Edition.lnk</path>
		<name>Sundered Eldritch Edition</name>
		<desc>Sundered is a chaotic hand­-drawn metroidvania where you resist or embrace ancient eldritch powers. Confront hordes of terrifying enemies in an ever-changing world inspired by the works of H.P. Lovecraft. Sundered is a challenging and unique take on a classic genre from the creators of Jotun, now with local co-op! You play Eshe, a wanderer in a ruined world, trapped in ever-­changing caverns filled with hordes of terrifying enemies. Harness the power of corrupted relics to defeat gigantic bosses, at the cost of your humanity. Resist or embrace. Sundered: Eldritch Edition includes the Magnate of the Gong update, adding local co-op multiplayer support for up to 4 players, along with new areas and a chaotic battle against the new Magnate of the Gong boss!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Sundered Eldritch Edition.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Sundered Eldritch Edition.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sundered Eldritch Edition.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.70</rating>
		<releasedate>201701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Thunder Lotus</developer>
		<publisher>Thunder Lotus</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shank 2.lnk</path>
		<name>Shank 2</name>
		<desc>The fan-favorite 2D brawler is back as ex-mob hit man Shank returns to action in Shank 2. With those closest to him under attack, Shank is once again forced on the offensive. Now he must put his trusty arsenal of handguns, shotguns, automatic weapons, chainsaws, machetes, grenades, plus all-new weaponry and moves to use in order to protect those close to him. The original game set a new standard for its visual style and Shank 2 raises the bar. Shank 2 expands on the original game’s amazing combat system to redefine the 2D side-scrolling brawler.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Shank 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Shank 2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Shank 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>201201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Klei Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./TRON RUNr.lnk</path>
		<name>TRON RUNr</name>
		<desc>Return to the world of TRON with TRON RUN/r, a new lightning fast, action-adventure runner with a twist! Blaze through dynamic circuits, facing-off against virulent adversaries while taking on all challengers. Pack your loadouts with dozens of combinations of cycles, suits and powerups. Hone your DISC and CYCLE skills on the 32 included levels, then challenge your friends to the grueling STREAM program that throws endless combinations of modes and levels at you until you crash - how long can you survive? The one who outlasts all tops the leaderboard!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/TRON RUNr.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/TRON RUNr.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/TRON RUNr.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.70</rating>
		<releasedate>201601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sanzaru Games</developer>
		<publisher>Disney Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Timespinner.lnk</path>
		<name>Timespinner</name>
		<desc>Travel back in time to change fate itself, in this beautifully crafted story-driven adventure, inspired by classic 90s action-platformers. Join timekeeper Lunais on her quest for revenge against the empire that killed her family, using time-bending powers to explore a vast, connected world. With her family murdered in front of her and the ancient Timespinner device destroyed, Lunais is suddenly transported into a unknown world, stranded with seemingly no hope of return. Using her power to control time, Lunais vows to take her revenge on the evil Lachiem Empire, but sometimes the course of history isn’t quite as black and white as it seems... Explore an intricate, connected world with beautifully drawn and detailed pixel art environments. Traverse between the barren present and luscious past of Lachiem, collecting elemental magic orbs and combining their power to destroy enemies with blades and spells.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Timespinner.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Timespinner.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Timespinner.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>201801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Lunar Ray Games</developer>
		<publisher>Chucklefish</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blaster Master Zero.lnk</path>
		<name>Blaster Master Zero</name>
		<desc>Mutant scum never learn! Blaster Master Zero is a 8-bit style top-down &amp; sideview 2D action-adventure game that hearkens back to the golden age of the NES. This game was created using the original 1988 title "Blaster Master" from Sunsoft as a base, with the addition of new areas and bosses, new gameplay elements such as extra sub-weapons, improved gameplay, a more robust scenario, refined and expanded exploration mechanics, and more. ・On the sideview maps, take control of the battle tank SOPHIA III and explore your surroundings as you search for the entrance to the dungeon where the area's boss lurks. ・Once you find a dungeon entrance, exit SOPHIA III and make your way inside as the hero Jason and take on the mutants that dwell within in top-down mode. ・Defeat the mid-bosses and area bosses to acquire new items, sub-weapons, upgrades to SOPHIA III and Jason's equipment, and new abilities and maneuvers that allow SOPHIA III to access new areas.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Blaster Master Zero.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Blaster Master Zero.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Blaster Master Zero.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>201901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Inti Creates</developer>
		<publisher>Inti Creates</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shakedown Hawaii.lnk</path>
		<name>Shakedown Hawaii</name>
		<desc>Shakedown: Hawaii is an open world action-adventure video game developed by Canadian studio Vblank Entertainment. Like its predecessor Retro City Rampage, it is a parody of multiple subjects, including retro games, 1980s pop culture, manipulative business practices, and Grand Theft Auto and similar games. Shakedown: Hawaii was released for Microsoft Windows, Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4, and PlayStation Vita on May 7, 2019. Shakedown: Hawaii features an open world island with 16-bit style graphics, a top-down perspective, over 200 accessible buildings, and a destructible environment. In addition to a story mode following the three main characters, the player can break away from missions to free-roam the map and extort local businesses, use a variety of weapons to cause chaos, attempt arcade-like challenges and mini-games, purchase real-estate in a market that fluctuates in response, steal cars, or purchase clothing from stores. Combat is similar to Retro City Rampage, and involves using a wide variety of weapons to destroy enemies, vehicles, and property.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Shakedown Hawaii.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Shakedown Hawaii.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Shakedown Hawaii.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>201901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vblank Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Vblank Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Galak-Z.lnk</path>
		<name>Galak-Z</name>
		<desc>Brand New features!! The Void DLC offers endless gameplay, Online Leaderboards, and a Daily Challenge that allows players to compete worldwide for the top score. Prepare for the bar to be raised on deep-space 2D dog-fighting! GALAK-Z is a modern, A.I. and physics-driven open-world action game, viewed through the lens of the classic 16-bit space shooter. Powered by the next-generation Cyntient AI platform, GALAK-Z puts players in control of anime-inspired spacecraft inhabiting procedurally generated worlds. In GALAK-Z both stealth and skill are required to defeat truly intelligent enemies. You will be forced to outsmart enemies that think, react and cooperate like seasoned pilots! Master your ship’s sublimely-honed controls as you blast enemies, unleash missile salvos, and even toss your opponents, mech-style, to their explosive demise. Recently added, Arcade Mode lets you replay failed missions any number of times without losing all of your saved progress. Rogue Mode retains GALAK-Z’s original white-knuckle roguelike challenge that harkens back to the 16-bit era of gaming.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Galak-Z.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Galak-Z.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Galak-Z.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>201501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>17-BIT</developer>
		<publisher>17-BIT</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Azure Striker Gunvolt.lnk</path>
		<name>Azure Striker Gunvolt</name>
		<desc>Azure Striker Gunvolt is a 2D action game featuring the talents of star creator Keiji Inafune as the Executive Producer and Action Supervisor. With the “septimal” power to create and manipulate lightning, Gunvolt faces off against the massive conglomerate known as the Sumeragi Group. Intense battles unfold against Sumeragi's ultra-powerful adepts (those who possess septimal powers) as Gunvolt fights to keep his nation free. SPEEDRUN MODE This new mode gives speedrunners around the world the chance to compete for the best time, with pre-determined settings put in place by the Gunvolt team to maximize efficiency for this challenging new mode. Future updates which will new add features and settings are already planned, so stayed tuned for information about that in the near future. LIGHTNING-BASED ACTION Use your trusty sidearm to tag enemies, then let loose a burst of electricity for massive damage.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Azure Striker Gunvolt.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Azure Striker Gunvolt.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Azure Striker Gunvolt.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>201501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Inti Creates</developer>
		<publisher>Inti Creates</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lara Croft GO.lnk</path>
		<name>Lara Croft GO</name>
		<desc>Lara Croft GO expands the turn-based puzzle gameplay and takes you on an adventure set in a long-forgotten world. Explore the ruins of an ancient civilization, discover hidden secrets and face deadly challenges as you uncover the myth of the Queen of Venom. A never-before-seen take on the iconic franchise featuring challenging gameplay, gorgeous visuals and a mesmerizing soundtrack, all at your fingertips.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Lara Croft GO.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Lara Croft GO.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Lara Croft GO.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>201612T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix Montréal</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shank.lnk</path>
		<name>Shank</name>
		<desc>Shank is the cult-classic revival of the sidescrolling beat-em-up. Play as Shank in an over-the-top grindhouse game, packed to the rim with enemies, bosses, combos, and more by the award-winning team at Klei Entertainment.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Shank.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Shank.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Shank.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>201008T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Klei Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>EA</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bubsy Paws on Fire.lnk</path>
		<name>Bubsy Paws on Fire</name>
		<desc>From the developers of the BIT.TRIP series comes Bubsy: Paws on Fire!, the latest and greatest in bobcat-based gaming. Bubsy is back in his greatest adventure yet! Featuring four playable characters with their own unique playstyles, new moves never before seen in a Bubsy title, and over 100 levels and variations, Paws on Fire is a game for Bubsy lovers everywhere!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Bubsy Paws on Fire.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Bubsy Paws on Fire.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Bubsy Paws on Fire.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>201905T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Choice Provisions</developer>
		<publisher>UFO Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Intrusion 2.lnk</path>
		<name>Intrusion 2</name>
		<desc>Intrusion 2 is an action platformer set in a sci-fi environment on a reserve planet occupied by a hostile military corporation conducting forbidden weapon research. Intrusion 2 is inspired by classic 16bit era sidescrollers and focuses on classic fast-paced action combined with modern physics and animation.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Intrusion 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Intrusion 2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Intrusion 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>201209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>VAP Games</developer>
		<publisher>VAP Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./KungFu Strike - The Warriors Rise.lnk</path>
		<name>KungFu Strike - The Warriors Rise</name>
		<desc>Taking its inspiration from ancient Chinese tales of revenge and retribution, then adding a dash of over-the-top martial arts and old school arcade fun, Kung Fu Strike features 28 stages of fast-paced combo-based fighting. Blend powerful punches, high kicks and perfectly timed blocks to pull off devastating combos, all thanks to a fluid combat system that turns brawling into an art form.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/KungFu Strike - The Warriors Rise.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/KungFu Strike - The Warriors Rise.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/KungFu Strike - The Warriors Rise.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>201207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Qooc Software</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Tribes</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Far Cry 3 Blood Dragon.lnk</path>
		<name>Far Cry 3 Blood Dragon</name>
		<desc>The year is 2007. It is the future. You are Sergeant Rex Colt: Mark IV Cyber Commando. The year is 2007 and Earth has been ravaged by a nuclear war which erupted in the 90s. The east vs. west conflict has raged for generations, and humanity continues to struggle to progress after a disastrous decade. New paths for peace must be found, and the US cyborg army may have found a solution: a powerful bioweapon on a distant island. Your mission is to gather information and figure out what the hell is going on.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Far Cry 3 Blood Dragon.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Far Cry 3 Blood Dragon.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Far Cry 3 Blood Dragon.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>201305T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft Montreal</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fire Pro Wrestling World.lnk</path>
		<name>Fire Pro Wrestling World</name>
		<desc>The greatest grappling game returns to take on the world! Customize every aspect of the match, from your wrestler to the ring itself, in your fight for the championship belt.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Fire Pro Wrestling World.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Fire Pro Wrestling World.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Fire Pro Wrestling World.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>201712T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Spike ChunSoft</developer>
		<publisher>ZEX Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting, Sports</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./RUINER.lnk</path>
		<name>RUINER</name>
		<desc>RUINER is a top-down action shooter created in the spirit of cult cyberpunk anime and game classics. RUINER is quick and brutal but sophisticated gameplay, original world with mature storyline and unique visual style.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/RUINER.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/RUINER.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/RUINER.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>201709T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Reikon Games</developer>
		<publisher>Devolver Digital</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Toren.lnk</path>
		<name>Toren</name>
		<desc>Toren brings poetry to life in an epic journey of growth, discovery and overcoming great hurdles. In Toren players guide Moonchild from birth to coming-of-age as she embarks on a dangerous journey of revelation and transformation. A distinct and unique art style, dark fantasy storytelling, innovative puzzles and beautiful soundtrack combine to make Toren a memorable gaming experience.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Toren.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Toren.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Toren.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>201505T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Swordtales</developer>
		<publisher>Versus Evil</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./FlatOut 4 - Total Insanity.lnk</path>
		<name>FlatOut 4 - Total Insanity</name>
		<desc>FlatOut 4: Total Insanity is a return to the franchise's adrenaline-pumping arcade destruction roots. Featuring an exciting blend of white-knuckle speed and wild out-of-control racing tracks, FlatOut 4 promises an intense death-defying demolition derby game featuring muscle cars, race cars, trucks and even a rocket boosted ice cream van!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/FlatOut 4 - Total Insanity.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/FlatOut 4 - Total Insanity.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/FlatOut 4 - Total Insanity.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>201703T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kylotonn Games</developer>
		<publisher>Big Ben Interactive, Strategy First</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Serious Sam HD - The First Encounter.lnk</path>
		<name>Serious Sam HD - The First Encounter</name>
		<desc>Serious Sam HD: The First Encounter is a visually upgraded and fully Steam supported remake version of the original high-adrenaline single-play and 16-player co-operative arcade-action FPS.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Serious Sam HD - The First Encounter.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Serious Sam HD - The First Encounter.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Serious Sam HD - The First Encounter.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>200911T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Croteam</developer>
		<publisher>Majesco Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Voodoo Vince Remastered.lnk</path>
		<name>Voodoo Vince Remastered</name>
		<desc>The classic character platformer is back after 13 years and newly remastered! Help Vince run, jump and fight his way through cemeteries, swamps and an evil carnival as he seeks to save his creator Madam Charmaine from the clutches of Kosmo The Inscrutable.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Voodoo Vince Remastered.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Voodoo Vince Remastered.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Voodoo Vince Remastered.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>201704T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Beep Games, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Beep Games, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Xeno Crisis.lnk</path>
		<name>Xeno Crisis</name>
		<desc>Xeno Crisis is an arena shooter in which one or two players take control of battle-hardened marines embarking on a deadly mission to confront an alien menace and get home alive! Run and gun your way through thousands of adversaries as you explore the devastated research outpost, searching for survivors, and ultimately facing the origin of the outpost's demise. Outpost 88 is divided into seven distinct areas, each being randomly generated with each play, meaning that your strategy must evolve on the fly if you're to succeed in your mission. Collect dog-tags from vanquished enemies to upgrade your equipment between areas and look out for special weapons which will give you a momentary advantage. +A faithful port of the hit 16 bit game with added extras. +Incredible pixel art from the legendary pixel artist, Henk Nieborg. +Intense FM chiptune soundtrack by Savaged Regime, originally created for the YM2612! +Two difficulty levels and three modes of play. +An arsenal of 10 weapons to master. +Play solo or local co-op with a friend!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Xeno Crisis.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Xeno Crisis.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Xeno Crisis.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20191201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bitmap Bureau</developer>
		<publisher>Independent</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pinball Arcade.lnk</path>
		<name>Pinball Arcade</name>
		<desc>Pinball Arcade by FarSight Studios features exact recreations of the all-time greatest pinball tables from Stern Pinball! The Pinball Arcade is the most realistic and comprehensive pinball game ever created. Please support us in our efforts to preserve these tables and join the indelible part of Americana that is pinball!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Pinball Arcade.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Pinball Arcade.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pinball Arcade.png</marquee>
		<rating>4.48</rating>
		<releasedate>20131104T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>FarSight Studios</developer>
		<publisher>FarSight Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./RetroMania Wrestling.lnk</path>
		<name>RetroMania Wrestling</name>
		<desc>RetroMania Wrestling is the official sequel to the classic arcade game Wrestlefest that was released in 1991 by Technos of Japan. RetroMania Wrestling will be a “pick up and play” arcade wrestling game with beautiful 2D sprites, incredible backgrounds and fast-paced arcade style game play. • 16 Unique, distinct playable wrestlers at launch (adding more post launch via DLC) • Over 15 Arenas • 3 distinct Game Modes; Story Mode, 10 Pounds of Gold, and Retro Rumble • 2-8 player local multiplayer • Several match types, including One-on-One matches, Tag Team matches, 6-Man Tag, 8-Man Tag, Cages matches with 3 different cage styles and Battle Royal.​• Ring entrances with entrance music • Strategic gameplay that is easy to pick up and play • Beautiful 2D pixel art animated sprites with over 700 frames of animation and animated backgrounds • Crowd chants that react to the action on screen • Commentary by Ian Riccaboni and Colt Cabana​.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/RetroMania Wrestling.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/RetroMania Wrestling.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/RetroMania Wrestling.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20211201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Retrosoft Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Retrosoft Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting, Sports</genre>
		<players>8</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Joe Danger.lnk</path>
		<name>Joe Danger</name>
		<desc>Can you put the world’s most determined stuntman back into the limelight? Combo, boost and pull ludicrous stunts as Joe attempts to race his way back into the record books in over 100 eye-popping levels. Leap school buses full of screaming kids and pools of ravenous sharks! Dodge spikes and mousetraps! Speed through coin dashes and beat Team Nasty in nip-and-tuck races!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Joe Danger.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Joe Danger.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Joe Danger.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>201007T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hello Games</developer>
		<publisher>Hello Games</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Axiom Verge.lnk</path>
		<name>Axiom Verge</name>
		<desc>Axiom Verge is a retro-styled 2D action game focused on unusual weaponry and exploration of an maze-like, infested world. You play as Trace, a relatively normal (if quirky) guy who suffers a near-fatal injury, after which he wakes up in a strange, unsettling new world that is both high-tech and incredibly ancient. Why is he here? Where are the world's inhabitants? And what is the mysterious force that seems intent on ending his life?</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Axiom Verge.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Axiom Verge.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Axiom Verge.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>201501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Thomas Happ Games</developer>
		<publisher>Thomas Happ Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pinball FX3.lnk</path>
		<name>Pinball FX3</name>
		<desc>Williams™ Pinball classics are now available -- and Fish Tales™ is yours for FREE! Zen is proud to bring these amazing games to players around the world. Enjoy! Zen Studios will continue to support Pinball FX3 with frequent content releases and new features!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Pinball FX3.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Pinball FX3.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pinball FX3.png</marquee>
		<rating>4.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20170926T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Zen Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Zen Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Life Simulation</genre>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="25557" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pure.lnk</path>
		<name>Pure</name>
		<desc>Developed by Black Rock Studio, Disney Interactive Studios' award-winning development studio in Brighton, England, Pure takes off-road racing to a new level. Featuring vertigo-inducing massive aerial jumps and spectacular airborne tricks in photo-realistic real-world locations all over the globe, Pure delivers heart-pounding experiences unique to the genre.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Pure.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Pure.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pure.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20080902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Black Rock Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Disney Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<genreid>1537</genreid>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SoulCalibur 6.lnk</path>
		<name>SoulCalibur 6</name>
		<desc>SOULCALIBUR VI represents the latest entry in the premier weapons-based, head-to-head fighting series and continues the epic struggle of warriors searching for the legendary Soul Swords. Taking place in the 16th century, revisit the events of the original SOULCALIBUR to uncover hidden truths.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/SoulCalibur 6.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/SoulCalibur 6.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/SoulCalibur 6.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>201810T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai Namco Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Valfaris Full Metal.lnk</path>
		<name>Valfaris Full Metal</name>
		<desc>A heavy metal infused 2D action-platformer and the next game from the team behind Unity Awards finalist, Slain: Back From Hell. Brutal combat. Deadly enemies. Stunning pixel art. Savage soundtrack. Get ready to rip the galaxy a new wormhole! After mysteriously vanishing from galactic charts, the fortress of Valfaris has suddenly reappeared in the orbit of a dying sun. Once a self-contained paradise, the grandiose citadel now plays host to an ever-growing darkness. Therion, a fearless and proud son of Valfaris, returns to his home to uncover the truth of its doomed fate and to challenge the arcane evil at its very heart.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Valfaris Full Metal.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Valfaris Full Metal.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Valfaris Full Metal.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>201101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Supergiant Games</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Bros.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sky Force Reloaded.lnk</path>
		<name>Sky Force Reloaded</name>
		<desc>Sky Force Reloaded is the spirit of the classic arcade shoot ‘em ups, captured with modern visuals and design. New entry in the series will keep you entertained with all the things you’ve came to love in scrolling shooters. Meaty explosions, incinerating lasers, collosal bosses and diverse aircrafts to pilot. Sky Force Reloaded is not your average scrolling shooter. It will draw you in with its beautiful environments and intense effects.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Sky Force Reloaded.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Sky Force Reloaded.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sky Force Reloaded.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.99</rating>
		<releasedate>20171201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infinite Dreams</developer>
		<publisher>Infinite Dreams</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Circuit Superstars.lnk</path>
		<name>Circuit Superstars</name>
		<desc>Circuit Superstars is a top-down, physics driven racing game for PC and consoles. It combines arcade-style racing with more realistic tactile driving physics, which brings together a whole range of styles and eras of motorsport. From 60s-inspired single-seaters to modern GTs, Circuit Superstars will feature vehicles and tracks from various motorsport eras.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Circuit Superstars.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Circuit Superstars.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Circuit Superstars.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20211201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Fire Games</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cloud Cutter.lnk</path>
		<name>Cloud Cutter</name>
		<desc>Cloud Cutter brings you classic arcade shoot ‘em up gameplay in top notch graphics. Cloud Cutter offers exactly what you expect and love in old-school scrolling shooters. Enjoy intense fast-paced explosive action full of epic destruction, arcade style power-ups, lasers and of course huge multi-stage boss fights. Blast your way through hundreds of enemies in a beautiful and ever-changing environment. Collect in-game power-ups to upgrade your ship and deal massive damage with a number of special powers. Master 13 detailed and immersive stages with challenging missions to complete that will push your pilot reflexes to their limits. Battle enormous and intimidating bosses.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Cloud Cutter.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Cloud Cutter.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Cloud Cutter.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20211201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Just Two Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Just Two Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Endless Memories.lnk</path>
		<name>Endless Memories</name>
		<desc>Explore a magical world of dreams in this epic 2D action-adventure that mixes a handcrafted non-linear world with ARPG elements. Join Rem in his journey through the dream world where the only way out is inside the mind of the Dreamers.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Endless Memories.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Endless Memories.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Endless Memories.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20201201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Homunculus Games</developer>
		<publisher>Homunculus Games</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, RPG</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Retrowave.lnk</path>
		<name>Retrowave</name>
		<desc>Neon lights, palm trees, synthwave, 80's supercars speeding down an endless highway... Welcome to the world of Retrowave!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Retrowave.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Retrowave.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Retrowave.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20201201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>RewindApp</developer>
		<publisher>RewindApp</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rival Megagun.lnk</path>
		<name>Rival Megagun</name>
		<desc>Rival Megagun is a competitive split-screen vertical shmup (or shoot 'em up, shooting game, STG) where you transform into a gigantic boss ship!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Rival Megagun.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Rival Megagun.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Rival Megagun.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20181201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Spacewave Software</developer>
		<publisher>Degica</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sky Rogue.lnk</path>
		<name>Sky Rogue</name>
		<desc>Sky Rogue is a fwooshy rogue-lite action flight simulator! Blow things up over land, sea, and air, on an infinite number of procedurally-generated islands. Choose one of a diverse set of aeros and kit it out with a dizzying array of weaponry. Go toe-to-toe with enemy aces or assault giant flying aircraft carriers and battleships, but watch out for volleys of missiles; when you die, you're dead.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Sky Rogue.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Sky Rogue.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sky Rogue.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20151201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nihilocrat</developer>
		<publisher>Fractal Phase</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Flight Simulator</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tempest 4000.lnk</path>
		<name>Tempest 4000</name>
		<desc>Tempest 4000 is a shoot 'em up video game. Players take a control of the Claw, a spacecraft that can shoot at enemies and obstructions. Levels take place on geometric prisms. The goal of the game is to survive each level by eliminating enemies as soon as possible and to achieve high scores for leaderboard positions. The game features one hundred levels and three game modes: standard, pure, and endurance. It is also available for the PC and Play Station 4. Yet another sequel to Dave Theurer's arcade classic.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Tempest 4000.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Tempest 4000.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tempest 4000.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20181201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LLamasoft</developer>
		<publisher>Atari SA</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gabriel Knight - Sins of the Fathers 20th Anniversary Edition.lnk</path>
		<name>Gabriel Knight - Sins of the Fathers 20th Anniversary Edition</name>
		<desc>This 20th Anniversary Edition is a remake of Gabriel Knight: Sins of the Fathers. It features new HD graphics, new puzzles, new voice acting, a remastered soundtrack by the original composer, and even some new locations. The game stays true to the original in terms of the story, and while it is still a 3rd-person point-and-click adventure game, it uses 3D graphics and character models instead of 2D graphics with sprites. Unlike the original, the game includes a hint book which lets you gradually (tip by tip until the actual solution) view tips on how to solve puzzles. There is a certain waiting time between checking the next available hint. Also, the hint book is integrated as Gabriel's diary where he keeps track of the story and his ideas which may provide clues to solving some puzzles or figuring what to do next. And finally, the book also contains extras which are tied to your current location.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Gabriel Knight - Sins of the Fathers 20th Anniversary Edition.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Gabriel Knight - Sins of the Fathers 20th Anniversary Edition.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Gabriel Knight - Sins of the Fathers 20th Anniversary Edition.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20140430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Phoenix Online Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Phoenix Online Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./AGS - Space Quest for Glory.lnk</path>
		<name>AGS - Space Quest for Glory</name>
		<desc>Fandmade remake Quest for Glory mixed with Space Quest using Adventure Gaming Studio engine. - A short little parody of two Sierra Classics! Battle the Labion Terror beast in a battle to the death! Get your plunger ready for the biggest battle the galaxy has ever seen!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/AGS - Space Quest for Glory.png</image>
		<video>./snap/AGS - Space Quest for Glory.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/AGS - Space Quest for Glory.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20190430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infamous Adventures</developer>
		<publisher>Fanmade</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./AGS - Quest for Glory II.lnk</path>
		<name>AGS - Quest for Glory II</name>
		<desc>Fandmade remake of Quest for Glory II using Adventure Gaming Studio engine. - AGD Interactive Ultimate Remake of Quest for Glory II: A Hero's work is never done! Save the ancient desert city of Shapir from the drreaded Elementals that threaten to destroy it.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/AGS - Quest for Glory II.png</image>
		<video>./snap/AGS - Quest for Glory II.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/AGS - Quest for Glory II.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20010430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AGD Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Fanmade</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./AGS - King Quest II.lnk</path>
		<name>AGS - King Quest II</name>
		<desc>Fandmade remake of King Quest II using Adventure Gaming Studio engine. - AGD Interactive Ultimate Remake of King's Quest II: Newly crowned King Graham is lonley of heart. A vision of a lovely maiden improsoned in a quartz tower leads him to the land of Kolyma on a quest to rescude his future bride!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/AGS - King Quest II.png</image>
		<video>./snap/AGS - King Quest II.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/AGS - King Quest II.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20010430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AGD Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Fanmade</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./The Journey Down - Chapter Two.lnk</path>
		<name>The Journey Down - Chapter Two</name>
		<desc>Chapter Two of The Journey Down, a classic point-and-click saga with an Afro-Caribbean vibe. Get ready to embark on an epic journey of brain-teasing adventure! Far below the noisy metropolis of St. Armando, Bwana follows in the footsteps of his lost father together with Kito and Lina. In their search for the mysterious Underland, they discover a dark conspiracy shrouding the fate of Captain Kaonandodo. In the second chapter, the plot thickens as our heroes plunge down into the mist below the Edge and wind up in the foggy and treacherous town of Port Artue where they find themselves cornered by pirates and on the run from the law. The Journey Down is a classic point-and-click saga with an Afro-Caribbean vibe.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/The Journey Down - Chapter Two.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/The Journey Down.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/The Journey Down.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20140430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SkyGoblin</developer>
		<publisher>SkyGoblin</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./The Journey Down - Chapter Three.lnk</path>
		<name>The Journey Down - Chapter Three</name>
		<desc>In the jungles of the Underland, scattered remnants of an ancient culture speak of a great evil that dwells in the shadowy depths of the Kwayerumoshi caves. But even the darkest secrets of this lost age are about to be revealed by the brave actions of three unlikely heroes. In the final chapter of The Journey Down, Bwana, Kito and Lina explore the vast reaches of the Underland and unravel its long-forgotten history. Their adventure comes to a bombastic conclusion when they learn the true nature of the Great Asili tree and the Armando Power Company. The Journey Down is a classic point-and-click saga with an Afro-Caribbean vibe. Get ready to embark on an epic journey of brain-teasing adventure! Features * A twisting tale of intriguing adventure * Tons of handpainted environments * An all original jazzy reggae soundtrack * A fully voiced cast * HD art and animations.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/The Journey Down - Chapter Three.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/The Journey Down.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/The Journey Down.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20170430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SkyGoblin</developer>
		<publisher>SkyGoblin</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./The Journey Down - Chapter One.lnk</path>
		<name>The Journey Down - Chapter One</name>
		<desc>In a shady corner of Kingsport Bay, at the outskirts of St Armando, Bwana and his trusted sidekick Kito struggle to make ends meet at their run-down gas station. Little do they know that they are about to be thrown into a spine-tingling adventure that will take them far from home and right into a twisting plot of corruption and danger. In the first chapter of The Journey Down, the search for a lost journal leads to forgotten secrets of the mysterious Underland. Follow Bwana and Kito as they puzzle their way forward and begin to uncover the true fate of their long lost father, Captain Kaonandodo. The Journey Down is a classic point-and-click saga with a black African twist. Get ready to embark on an epic journey of laughs and brain-teasing adventure!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/The Journey Down - Chapter One.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/The Journey Down.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/The Journey Down.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20130430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SkyGoblin</developer>
		<publisher>SkyGoblin</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./AGS - King Quest I.lnk</path>
		<name>AGS - King Quest I</name>
		<desc>Fandmade remake of King Quest I using Adventure Gaming Studio engine. - AGD Interactive Ultimate Remake of King's Quest I: A dying King Edward entrusts his finest knight to seek the Three Lost Treasures of Daventry.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/AGS - King Quest I.png</image>
		<video>./snap/AGS - King Quest I.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/AGS - King Quest I.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20010430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AGD Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Fanmade</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./AGS - King Quest III.lnk</path>
		<name>AGS - King Quest III</name>
		<desc>Fandmade remake of King Quest III using Adventure Gaming Studio engine. - AGD Interactive Ultimate Remake of King's Quest III: To Heir is Human! Join Gwydion as he seeks to escape the bonds of slavery from his master, the evil wizard Mananann.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/AGS - King Quest III.png</image>
		<video>./snap/AGS - King Quest III.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/AGS - King Quest III.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20010430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AGD Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Fanmade</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./AGS - Resonance.lnk</path>
		<name>AGS - Resonance</name>
		<desc>Fandmade Resonance using Adventure Gaming Studio engine. - When a brilliant particle physicist dies unexpectedly, the race is on to secure his terrible new technology before it falls into the wrong hands. The lives of four playable characters become entangled as they fight against the clock to find the dead scientist’s secret vault.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/AGS - Resonance.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/AGS - Resonance.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/AGS - Resonance.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20120430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wadjet Eye Games</developer>
		<publisher>Fanmade</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./AGS - Space Quest II.lnk</path>
		<name>AGS - Space Quest II</name>
		<desc>Fandmade remake Space Quest II using Adventure Gaming Studio engine. - Infamous Adventure's remake of the classic 1987 Sierra game "Space Quest II" by The Two Guys from Andromeda, Scott Murphy and Mark Crowe!  Join Roger Wilco on an intergalactic adventure as he is pursued by the agents of the sinister Sludge Vohaul! Lovingly recrafted in simulated VGA colors!.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/AGS - Space Quest II.png</image>
		<video>./snap/AGS - Space Quest II.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/AGS - Space Quest II.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20190430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infamous Adventures</developer>
		<publisher>Fanmade</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mortal Kombat Komplete Edition.lnk</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat Komplete Edition</name>
		<desc>After centuries of Mortal Kombat, Emperor Shao Kahn has finally defeated Raiden and his allies. Faced with extinction, Raiden has one last chance to save Earthrealm. To undo the Emperor's victory, he must strike Shao Kahn where he is vulnerable...the Past. Driven by an all new graphics engine, the fan favorite series is back and presented in more gory detail than ever before.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Mortal Kombat Komplete Edition.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Mortal Kombat Komplete Edition.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Mortal Kombat Komplete Edition.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20131201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NetherRealm Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Bros</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Halo - Spartan Strike.lnk</path>
		<name>Halo - Spartan Strike</name>
		<desc>Halo: Spartan Strike makes you a Spartan supersoldier battling evil forces. Delve into 30 challenging missions through cities and jungles using a devastating arsenal of weapons, abilities and vehicles including the iconic Warthog against the Covenant and Promethean enemies. Be the Spartan and deny your foes the conquest of Earth.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Halo - Spartan Strike.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Halo - Spartan Strike.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Halo - Spartan Strike.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20141201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>353 Industries</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hotshot Racing.lnk</path>
		<name>Hotshot Racing</name>
		<desc>Hotshot Racing is a blisteringly fast arcade-style racing game fusing drift handling, razor-sharp retro visuals and an incredible sense of speed to create an exhilarating driving experience. Developed by racing game veterans SUMO Nottingham and Lucky Mountain Games, Hotshot Racing is an all-new driving experience which revives the classic arcade gameplay of the 90s and thrusts it into the modern era. 16 racing circuits provide the twists, turns and straights conducive to searingly quick racing.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Hotshot Racing.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Hotshot Racing.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Hotshot Racing.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20201201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Lucky Mountain Games</developer>
		<publisher>Curve Digital</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gauntlet Slayer Edition.lnk</path>
		<name>Gauntlet Slayer Edition</name>
		<desc>Gauntlet is a top-down dungeon crawler and an entry in the long-running Gauntlet series. The game supports up to four online or local players working cooperatively, each using a different one of the four available hero types: Elf, Valkyrie, Warrior and Wizard.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Gauntlet Slayer Edition.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Gauntlet Slayer Edition.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Gauntlet Slayer Edition.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20141101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arrowhead Game Studios</developer>
		<publisher>WB Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Horizon Chase Turbo.lnk</path>
		<name>Horizon Chase Turbo</name>
		<desc>Horizon Chase Turbo is a racing game inspired by the great hits of the 80's and 90's: Out Run, Lotus Turbo Challenge, Top Gear (SNES), Rush, among others. Each curve and each lap in Horizon Chase Turbo recreates classic arcade gameplay and offers you unbound speed limits of fun. Full throttle on and enjoy!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Horizon.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Horizon chase turbo.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Horizon.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20180515T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aquiris Game Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Aquiris Game Studio</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<md5>d674e02c2a0330d1129df0fe0c75b717</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Fighter X Tekken.lnk</path>
		<name>Street Fighter X Tekken</name>
		<desc>The game features characters from both the Street Fighter franchise and Namco's Tekken series. In the game, each player selects two characters respectively and face other as duos in tag team fighting matches, with the objective to knock out one of the members from the opposing team (deplete the opponent's health).</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Street Fighter X Tekken.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Street Fighter X Tekken.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Street Fighter X Tekken.png</marquee>
		<rating>1.0</rating>
		<releasedate>20121912T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting Game</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Torchlight 2.lnk</path>
		<name>Torchlight 2</name>
		<desc>After the events of the first game, Alchemist, one of the three main classes, is corrupted by the Emberblight from the heart of Ordrak, the main source of corruption beneath the town of Torchlight. Now he is on a rampage for taking the power of guardians and breaking the balance of elements. New heroes arrive to rise up against his madness with the help of the destroyer and the vanquisher, other two playable characters from the first game. Many elements from the original hack-and-slash RPG Torchlight (fishing, pets, etc) make a return in the sequel, including the randomly generated dungeons. There are more classes, pets and weapon types and the locations to visit are more varied. There are now snowy areas, deserts, forests etc. Instead of the dungeon descending structure of the original game, the sequel has large above-ground environments with hub towns and each one has a couple of separate dungeons that consist of one floor or multiple ones. Unlike the first game multiplayer is now supported through cooperative sessions for up to six players, both locally and online. There are three acts and an epilogue. Other new elements are time of day cycles, an updated interface design, and various weather effects. The character appearance can be fully customized based on various attributes.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Torchlight 2.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Torchlight 2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Torchlight 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>3.76</rating>
		<releasedate>20120920T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Runic Games</developer>
		<publisher>Runic Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Trackmania Turbo.lnk</path>
		<name>Trackmania Turbo</name>
		<desc>TrackMania: Turbo features gameplay akin to that of previous games in the series. The player can race on over 200 different tracks, across four different locations, namely Rollercoaster Lagoon, International Stadium, Canyon Grand Drift, and Valley Down and Dirty. Similar to previous games, the game moves at a very high pace with a high focus on stunts. The game's developer said that "They wanted Trackmania Turbo to be an arcade game" Various modes are set to appear in the game, including a campaign and a mode called Double Driver, which is a cooperative multiplayer mode, in which two players are controlling the same car.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Trackmania Turbo.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Trackmania Turbo.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Trackmania Turbo.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20161201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nadeo</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ultimate Marvel vs. Capcom 3.lnk</path>
		<name>Ultimate Marvel vs. Capcom 3</name>
		<desc>Marvel and Capcom join forces to deliver the most frenetic 3 vs. 3 tag battles ever with Ultimate Marvel vs. Capcom 3. This release comes fully loaded, including all previous DLC, and the Marvel vs. Capcom: Official Complete Works. Select some of the most iconic Marvel and Capcom characters, and customize your team with "Heroes and Heralds" mode. Once you've honed your skills, hop online and go head-to-head against players from around the world to see who is the strongest in the universe.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ultimate Marvel vs. Capcom 3.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Ultimate Marvel vs. Capcom 3.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ultimate Marvel vs. Capcom 3.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20171201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Vikings - Wolves of Midgard.lnk</path>
		<name>Vikings - Wolves of Midgard</name>
		<desc>Vikings – Wolves of Midgard takes you to the Shores of Midgard, a world based upon the mythology and history of the Vikings, but with a fantasy twist. Battle the fearsome Jotan, hordes of terrifying undead monstrosities and the beasts of Ragnarok, as you strive to survive the growing cold of Fimbulwinter.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Vikings - Wolves of Midgard.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Vikings - Wolves of Midgard.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Vikings - Wolves of Midgard.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>20171201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Games Farm</developer>
		<publisher>Kalypso Media</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Double Dragon Neon.lnk</path>
		<name>Double Dragon Neon</name>
		<desc>BRO-TACULAR! Legendary martial artists, Billy and Jimmy Lee return in this creative re-imagining of the classic beat ‘em up, Double Dragon Neon.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Double Dragon Neon.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Double Dragon Neon.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Double Dragon Neon.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20141201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Abstraction Games</developer>
		<publisher>Majesco Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Titan Quest Anniversary.lnk</path>
		<name>Titan Quest Anniversary</name>
		<desc>For its 10 year anniversary, Titan Quest will shine in new splendour. This Anniversary Edition combines both Titan Quest and Titan Quest Immortal Throne in one game, and has been given a massive overhaul for the ultimate ARPG experience. -- Anniversary Edition update -- - Restored and improved multiplayer functionality, including new features like a built-in voice chat and NAT resolving for best multiplayer connectivity - Support for more resolutions, larger camera distance and scaleable UI size - Improved performance and general stability - Support for modders through new modding options and a fully integrated Steam Workshop - Complete balance rework with improvements to all Masteries, damage types, unique items and sets - Countless bug fixes and other improvements, including ten years’ worth of community fixes - Increased challenges and rewards for larger parties and on higher difficulty levels - Dozens of new heroes and bosses to encounter.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Titan Quest Anniversary.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Titan Quest Anniversary.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Titan Quest Anniversary.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>201601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>THQ Nordic</developer>
		<publisher>THQ Nortic</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>6</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grim Dawn.lnk</path>
		<name>Grim Dawn</name>
		<desc>Delve deep into the oil rig city of Ravensdale. A medieval metropolis that went bonkers after the people discovered goop - a raw fluid that provided energy, skin cream, bread spread and powered diesel engines. And it turned the people of Ravensdale into raging, bloodthirsty monsters. Lucky for them they have you, leading a pack of lunatic knights on a killing spree to save the city. Rogue Stormers combines classic run 'n' gun gameplay with a modern art style, and twin stick shooter configuration. Your goal is to fight and beat the ultimate evil threatening Ravensdale...But in order to beat him, you need to fight your way through 7 increasingly challenging levels. If you die, you'll be back at square one. Earned perks are yours to keep, allowing your character to grow stronger with each new raid.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Grim Dawn.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Grim Dawn.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Grim Dawn.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20161201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crate Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Crate Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./River City Ransom - Underground.lnk</path>
		<name>River City Ransom - Underground</name>
		<desc>River City Ransom: Underground is a continuation of the quirky beat'em up series. The plot takes place 20 years after the original River City Ransom. Alex and Ryan, retired from their fighting days, are now running an auto repair shop, while the infamous Slick rots in jail. After a mysterious kidnapping jolts the town, the gang of high-schoolers known as "The Flock" is framed for the abduction, but Alex and Ryan figure this has Slick's handiwork all over it. It's up to the player to find out what truly is going on in River City and stop the culprit once and for all. The game is a beat 'em up with a lot of similarities to the original River City Ransom.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/River City Ransom - Underground.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/River City Ransom - Underground.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/River City Ransom - Underground.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>201701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Conatus Creative</developer>
		<publisher>Conatus Creative</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rogue Stormers.lnk</path>
		<name>Rogue Stormers</name>
		<desc>Delve deep into the oil rig city of Ravensdale. A medieval metropolis that went bonkers after the people discovered goop - a raw fluid that provided energy, skin cream, bread spread and powered diesel engines. And it turned the people of Ravensdale into raging, bloodthirsty monsters. Lucky for them they have you, leading a pack of lunatic knights on a killing spree to save the city. Rogue Stormers combines classic run 'n' gun gameplay with a modern art style, and twin stick shooter configuration. Your goal is to fight and beat the ultimate evil threatening Ravensdale...But in order to beat him, you need to fight your way through 7 increasingly challenging levels. If you die, you'll be back at square one. Earned perks are yours to keep, allowing your character to grow stronger with each new raid.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Rogue Stormers.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Rogue Stormers.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Rogue Stormers.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20161201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Black Forest Games</developer>
		<publisher>Black Forest Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Unruly Heroes.lnk</path>
		<name>Unruly Heroes</name>
		<desc>The sacred scroll preserving harmony in our world has been torn up and scattered to the winds. Now, strange and terrifying creatures are sowing discord and chaos throughout the land.Only four totally opposed, implausible heroes can turn back the tide: Sanzang the wise, Wukong the fearless monkey, Kihong the greedy pig, and Sandmonk the sensitive brute. On their journey westward, they will travel to fantastical worlds to gather the pieces of the scroll and fight an army of evil creatures.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Unruly Heroes.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Unruly Heroes.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Unruly Heroes.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20191201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Magic Design Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Magic Design Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mantis Burn Racing.lnk</path>
		<name>Mantis Burn Racing</name>
		<desc>The race is on in Mantis Burn Racing, where fast-paced bumper-to-bumper racing combines with intuitive, tactile gameplay and stunning visuals in one of the best-looking and most immersive top-down racers around. Drive incredible built-for-racing vehicles across highly detailed, visually stunning tracks, in high-risk, high-speed races where winning is everything. Prove your skills in an extensive career mode and take on friends with 4-player local split-screen racing and online modes for up to 8 players in ‘one-more-go’ style competitive racing. With a RPG-style upgrade system providing players with deep tactical choices and excellent replay-ability, this is racing at its rawest but most exciting!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Mantis Burn Racing.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Mantis Burn Racing.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Mantis Burn Racing.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>201601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>VooFoo Studios</developer>
		<publisher>VooFoo Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Warhammer - Chaosbane.lnk</path>
		<name>Warhammer - Chaosbane</name>
		<desc>In a world ravaged by war and dominated by magic, you are the last hope for the Empire of Man against the Chaos hordes. Playing solo or with up to 4 in local or online co-op, choose a hero from 4 character classes with unique and complementary skills, and prepare for epic battles wielding some of the most powerful artefacts of the Old World. • THE FIRST HACK AND SLASH set in the Warhammer Fantasy world, told through an all-new story written by Mike Lee (a Black Library author) and featuring a soundtrack composed by Chance Thomas. • FEROCIOUS BATTLES: from the sewers of Nuln to the ruined streets of Praag, fight your way through monster hordes using over 180 different powers. Activate your bloodlust, a devastating skill, to escape the most perilous situations. • 4 CHARACTER CLASSES, each with unique skills and customisation: a soldier of the Empire who can take heavy damage, a Dwarf specialising in melee combat, a High Elf who deals ranged damage by manipulating magic or a Wood Elf who lays deadly traps and wields the bow like no other!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Warhammer - Chaosbane.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Warhammer - Chaosbane.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Warhammer - Chaosbane.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20191201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eko Software</developer>
		<publisher>BigBen Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Anima - The Reign of Darkness.lnk</path>
		<name>Anima - The Reign of Darkness</name>
		<desc>Anima is an action RPG (hack’n slash) videogame inspired by the greatest old school games and made with passion by RPG lovers for RPG lovers.
After the great success achieved on mobile devices, anima finally arrives on PC with brand new graphics and gameplay!
Conquer the single player campaign with potentially infinite game difficulties, follow the storyline or simply go on, slash enemies, loot items and improve your character!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Anima - The Reign of Darkness.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Anima - The Reign of Darkness.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Anima - The Reign of Darkness.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20211201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Redeev</developer>
		<publisher>Redeev</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cuphead.lnk</path>
		<name>Cuphead</name>
		<desc>Cuphead is a run and gun platform indie video game developed and published by StudioMDHR Entertainment. As the titular character Cuphead, the player fights a series of bosses in order to repay a debt to the devil.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Cuphead.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Cuphead.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Cuphead.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20171201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>StudioMDHR Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>StudioMDHR Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ghosts 'n Goblins Resurrection.lnk</path>
		<name>Ghosts 'n Goblins Resurrection</name>
		<desc>Watch as this nostalgic yet completely re-imagined storybook world unravels before your very eyes. Taking cues from both Ghosts 'n Goblins and Ghouls 'n Ghosts and giving birth to something entirely new, Resurrection is a title worthy of its name. Don't be fooled—this picturesque storybook world, while gorgeous, is a love-letter to the original titles and maintains the same punishing game play that fans have come to expect. So go on and test your mettle, for the gauntlet has been thrown!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ghosts 'n Goblins Resurrection.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Ghosts 'n Goblins Resurrection.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ghosts 'n Goblins Resurrection.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20211201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Minecraft Dungeons.lnk</path>
		<name>Minecraft Dungeons</name>
		<desc>Minecraft Dungeons is a dungeon crawler video game developed by Mojang Studios and Double Eleven and published by Xbox Game Studios. It is based on Minecraft and was released for Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4, Windows, and Xbox One on May 26, 2020. The game received lukewarm reviews; many deemed the game fun and charming, with general praise directed at its visuals and music. However, its simple gameplay and use of procedural generation received more mixed reception, with its short story and lack of depth also being met with criticism.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Minecraft Dungeons.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Minecraft Dungeons.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Minecraft Dungeons.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20201201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Double Eleven, Mojang</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nine Parchments.lnk</path>
		<name>Nine Parchments</name>
		<desc>Nine Parchments is a co-operative blast 'em up game of magical mayhem from Frozenbyte, creators of the Trine series! Runaway apprentice wizards seize the opportunity to complete their spellbooks by going after the lost Nine Parchments. As the would-be wizards rapidly acquire powerful new spells without learning proper safety measures, it's natural their hasty progress results in plenty of deadly accidents... Nine Parchments combines real-time spell-shooting action with RPG elements - level up your character and collect magical loot, filling your wardrobe with a myriad of wizard hats and powerful staves. Features - Dozens of spells for you to discover and master - Unlock new playable characters with quests - Find fashionable Hats and powerful Staves - Level up and improve your characters with their Skill Trees - Resurrection and Friendly Fire: Help and hinder your friends - Battle strange creatures and mighty bosses in the beautiful Trine world - Online and local co-op with 1-4 players.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Nine Parchments.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Nine Parchments.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Nine Parchments.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.90</rating>
		<releasedate>20171201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Frozenbyte</developer>
		<publisher>Frozenbyte</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./R-Type Dimensions.lnk</path>
		<name>R-Type Dimensions EX</name>
		<desc>The coin-op classics, R-Type &amp; R-Type II, are together on Steam! Fight through all 14 Bydo-infested stages in retro 2D graphics or shiny 3D graphics - and swap back and forth with the touch of a button 'on-the-fly'. The new 3D graphics are accompanied by fully re-imagined arrangements of the timeless R-Type music tracks! The classic game-play remains untouched while the new Infinite game mode allows continuous progression from game start to final boss... the Bydo will not evade you this time! Both game modes can be played as single player or local multiplayer. Pull yourself together, save the earth and strike down the Evil Bydo Empire!!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/R-Type.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/R-Type.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/R-Type.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20181128T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tozai Games</developer>
		<publisher>Tozai Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<md5>6b306021f667bf5fcb32145a2f45bbff</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./R-Type Final 2.lnk</path>
		<name>R-Type Final 2</name>
		<desc>R-Type Final 2 is a horizontal-scrolling shooter video game developed and published by Granzella. Part of Irem's long-running R-Type series, it is a sequel to R-Type Final released in 2004, and the first R-Type game in over a decade, after the release of R-Type Tactics II: Operation Bitter Chocolate in 2009. The game was released for the Microsoft Windows, Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4, Xbox One, and Xbox Series X/S on April 29, 2021. The western versions of the game are published by NIS America, and are set to release on April 30, 2021. R-Type Final 2 is the first game in the series to be released outside of Japan since R-Type Dimensions in 2009.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/R-Type Final 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/R-Type Final 2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/R-Type Final 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20211201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Granzella</developer>
		<publisher>NIIS America Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Renegade Ops Collection.lnk</path>
		<name>Renegade Ops Collection</name>
		<desc>Destruction just got awesome. In Renegade Ops you must defeat Inferno, a madman intent on global domination. Destroy enemies across a range of stunning environments using a wide variety of vehicles. Players have the choice to fight alone in single player mode, team up offline with two-player split screen or join the dynamic 4-player online co-op experience. Blast your way through enemy lines by working together, or compete for achievements as you and your friends aim to top the online leader boards.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Renegade Ops Collection.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Renegade Ops Collection.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Renegade Ops Collection.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20111201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Avalanche Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Riptide GP Renegade.lnk</path>
		<name>Riptide GP Renegade</name>
		<desc>Experience the future of illicit hydrojet racing, where armored riders kick out death-defying stunts over massive waterfalls, dodge cops through public waterways, and boost at breakneck speeds across surging waves. You are a hydrojet rider, framed and cast out from the Riptide GP league, forced to race illegally through city waterways, flooded ruins, and churning factory machinery in an effort to reclaim your reputation and your title. Play through the single player career to unlock new vehicles, playable characters, and customization features as you take down bosses and build your crew. Then, take your skills online for the ultimate test as you battle opponents around the world in 8-player online matches.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Riptide GP Renegade.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Riptide GP Renegade.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Riptide GP Renegade.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20161201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vector Unit</developer>
		<publisher>Vector Unit</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>8</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lara Croft and the Guardian of Light.lnk</path>
		<name>Lara Croft and the Guardian of Light</name>
		<desc>Lara Croft and the Guardian of Light is a fixed-camera 3D platform with an isometric viewpoint action video game developed by Crystal Dynamics and published by Square Enix for the PC, PlayStation Network, Xbox Live Arcade and the iOS as part of the Tomb Raider series for digital download. Unlike previous games in the series, the game does not carry the Tomb Raider brand and has a heavy emphasis on cooperative gameplay. In multiplayer, players take the role as either Lara Croft or a 2,000 year old Mayan warrior named Totec. They must work together in order to stop the evil spirit Xolotl and retrieve the Mirror of Smoke. A single-player campaign mode is available that does not include the non-playable character AI following or helping Lara.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Lara Croft and the Guardian of Light.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Lara Croft and the Guardian of Light.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Lara Croft and the Guardian of Light.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20101201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crystal Dynamics</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
</gameList>
